{"The CDC currently reports 99031 deaths. In general the discrepancies in death counts between different sources are small and explicable. The death toll stands at roughly 100000 people today.": [["CDC", "ORG"], ["99031", "CARDINAL"], ["roughly 100000", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"]], "States reported 1121 deaths a small rise from last Tuesday. Southern states reported 640 of those deaths. https://t.co/YASGRTT4ux": [["States", "GPE"], ["1121", "CARDINAL"], ["last Tuesday", "DATE"], ["Southern", "NORP"], ["640", "CARDINAL"]], "Politically Correct Woman (Almost) Uses Pandemic as Excuse Not to Reuse Plastic Bag https://t.co/thF8GuNFPe #coronavirus #nashville": [], "#IndiaFightsCorona: We have 1524 #COVID testing laboratories in India and as on 25th August 2020 36827520 tests have been done : @ProfBhargava DG @ICMRDELHI #StaySafe #IndiaWillWin https://t.co/Yh3ZxknnhZ": [["1524", "CARDINAL"], ["India", "GPE"], ["25th August 2020", "DATE"]], "Populous states can generate large case counts but if you look at the new cases per million today 9 smaller states are showing more cases per million than California or Texas: AL AR ID KS KY LA MS NV and SC. https://t.co/1pYW6cWRaS": [["million", "CARDINAL"], ["9", "CARDINAL"], ["million", "CARDINAL"], ["California", "GPE"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["AL AR", "ORG"], ["KS KY LA MS NV", "ORG"], ["SC", "ORG"]], "Covid Act Now found \"on average each person in Illinois with COVID-19 is infecting 1.11 other people. Data shows that the infection growth rate has declined over time this factors in the stay-at-home order and other restrictions put in place.\" https://t.co/hhigDd24fE": [["Illinois", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "ORG"], ["1.11", "CARDINAL"]], "If you tested positive for #COVID19 and have no symptoms stay home and away from other people. Learn more about CDC’s recommendations about when you can be around others after COVID-19 infection: https://t.co/z5kkXpqkYb. https://t.co/9PaMy0Rxaf": [["CDC", "ORG"]], "Obama Calls Trump’s Coronavirus Response A Chaotic Disaster https://t.co/DeDqZEhAsB": [["Obama", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]], "???Clearly, the Obama administration did not leave any kind of game plan for something like this.??�": [["Obama", "PERSON"]], "Retraction—Hydroxychloroquine or chloroquine with or without a macrolide for treatment of COVID-19: a multinational registry analysis - The Lancet https://t.co/L5V2x6G9or": [["Hydroxychloroquine", "PRODUCT"]], "Take simple daily precautions to help prevent the spread of respiratory illnesses like #COVID19. Learn how to protect yourself from coronavirus (COVID-19): https://t.co/uArGZTrH5L. https://t.co/biZTxtUKyK": [], "The NBA is poised to restart this month. In March we reported on how the Utah Jazz got 58 coronavirus tests in a matter of hours at a time when U.S. testing was sluggish. https://t.co/I8YjjrNoTh https://t.co/o0Nk6gpyos": [["NBA", "ORG"], ["this month", "DATE"], ["March", "DATE"], ["the Utah Jazz", "ORG"], ["58", "CARDINAL"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "We just announced that the first participants in each age cohort have been dosed in the Phase 2 study of our mRNA vaccine (mRNA-1273) against novel coronavirus. Read more: https://t.co/woPlKz1bZC #mRNA https://t.co/9VGUoJu5cS": [["2", "CARDINAL"]], "#CoronaVirusUpdates #IndiaFightsCorona More than 6 lakh tests done for 3rd successive day. Cumulative testing as on date has reached 22149351. #COVID19 Tests Per Million (TPM) cross 16000.": [["3rd successive day", "DATE"], ["22149351", "CARDINAL"], ["16000", "CARDINAL"]], "Protect yourself and others from #COVID19 when using public transportation. Practice social distancing avoid touching surfaces and practice hand hygiene. Learn more: https://t.co/0vhHD4uFv9. https://t.co/D8YSeE3vXv": [], "As of 18 August 2020 8AM till now there have been a total of 4687 #COVID19 positive cases &amp; 17 #COVID_19 related deaths in #Manipur #COVID__19 #COVIDー19 #COVID19India #COVIDUpdates #CoronaUpdates #Corona #coronavirus #CoronavirusIndia #CoronavirusUpdates #CoronavirusPandemic https://t.co/au9kzAchGh": [["18 August 2020", "DATE"], ["4687", "CARDINAL"], ["17", "CARDINAL"]], "Because of Donald Trump's negligence and incompetence:\n \n- More than 110,000 people have died\n- We have nearly 2 million cases of COVID-19\n- Over 20 million Americans are out of work\n \nAnd yet he’s patting himself on the back. Unbelievable.": [["Donald Trump's", "PERSON"], ["More than 110,000", "CARDINAL"], ["2 million", "CARDINAL"], ["20 million", "CARDINAL"], ["Americans", "NORP"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona India continues to scale new peaks in #COVID19 tests! More than 11.70 lakh samples tested daily for 2 consecutive days. No other country has achieved these levels of very high daily testing. @PMOIndia @drharshvardhan @AshwiniKChoubey @PIB_India @DDNewslive": [["#IndiaFightsCorona India", "ORG"], ["More than 11.70", "CARDINAL"], ["daily", "DATE"], ["2 consecutive days", "DATE"]], "We just announced that we have shipped vials of mRNA-1273 the Company’s vaccine against the novel coronavirus to the NIH to be used in the planned Phase 1 study in the U.S. https://t.co/jNarQEkGhr https://t.co/o7EoaYeQH1": [["NIH", "ORG"], ["Phase 1", "EVENT"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "Multiple Facebook posts claim that “Aussies will be fined if they are found to be talking about conspiracies to do with [COVID-19]”. The posts included a screenshot of a segment from an Australian breakfast television show as evidence for the claim.": [["Facebook", "ORG"], ["Aussies", "NORP"], ["Australian", "NORP"]], "No Nobel Prize laureate Tasuku Honjo didn't say the coronavirus is \"not natural\" as a post on Facebook claims. In fact Professor Honjo said he's \"greatly saddened\" his name was used to spread misinformation. This and more in the latest #CoronaCheck: https://t.co/rLcTuIcIHO https://t.co/WdoocCiXFu": [["Nobel Prize", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Tasuku Honjo", "PERSON"], ["Facebook", "ORG"], ["Honjo", "PERSON"]], "The NZ COVID Tracker app will remain important and useful at Alert level 1. People are encouraged to download the app or a similar one or keep a record of where you’re going to be.": [["NZ COVID Tracker", "PRODUCT"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "BREAKING NEWS# The president Cryill Ramaphosa has asked all foreign nations to depart south Africa before 21 june 2020 due to increasing cases of COVID 19 .": [["Cryill Ramaphosa", "PERSON"], ["Africa", "LOC"], ["21 june 2020", "DATE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"]], "We are delighted that 78 high- and upper-middle countries and economies have now confirmed they will participate in the COVAX Facility and the number is growing. I urge those who have not yet joined to do so by the 18th of September-@DrTedros #COVID19": [["78", "CARDINAL"], ["the COVAX Facility", "ORG"], ["the 18th of September", "DATE"]], "Very intriguing possibility that mood changes and anxiety may be a function of invasion of the #coronavirus into the CNS and brain. https://t.co/q5kwqJmFRt": [], "Elon Musck To New Baby; Get A Job Kid! https://t.co/bc8Re0Ai3Y #christmas #covid19 #elonmusk #achristmascarol": [["Elon Musck", "PERSON"]], "_A new alcohol-free sanitizer has been developed by the Dedan Kimathi University in Kenya._": [["the Dedan Kimathi University", "ORG"], ["Kenya._", "GPE"]], "Just Appendix B gathering all the state orders on testing was a huge chunk of work. Same goes for Appendix D an evaluation of the accessibility of the CDC's Data Tracker.": [["CDC", "ORG"], ["Data Tracker", "PRODUCT"]], "Yesterday our laboratories completed 2899 tests of those 726 were testing of people in managed isolation and quarantine for the routine testing on either days 3 or 12 of their stay. That brings the total number of tests completed to date to 436233.": [["Yesterday", "DATE"], ["2899", "CARDINAL"], ["726", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["12", "CARDINAL"], ["436233", "CARDINAL"]], "Reusing #N95 masks? NIH found vaporized hydrogen peroxide UV light and heat to be effective sanitizers. https://t.co/2RgFWeSLrv #coronavirus https://t.co/Lz1IaMdPZg": [["NIH", "ORG"]], ".@realDonaldTrump has shifted his focus at different moments in the #CoronavirusOutbreak. We updated our running timeline of his response to the virus. https://t.co/pgXjssaRCB Reply to us with any recent Trump moments you think belong on this running list. https://t.co/g4WYcppDSO": [["CoronavirusOutbreak", "PRODUCT"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]], "Doctored image of President Donald Trump shared claiming he asked people to chant Hare Krishna Hare Rama.": [["Donald Trump", "PERSON"], ["Hare Krishna Hare Rama", "PERSON"]], "This #FourthOfJuly weekend if you choose to spend time outdoors at an event or gathering stay 6 ft apart &amp; wear a cloth face cover to slow the spread of #COVID19. Learn more at https://t.co/c4F0aouMLd. https://t.co/u5tTl3m572": [["This #FourthOfJuly weekend", "DATE"]], "CDC Recommends Mothers Stop Breastfeeding To Boost Vaccine Efficacy": [["CDC", "ORG"]], "Singapore Airlines Haults All Flights Due To Coronavirus Outbreak https://t.co/ANHxHm1DPK": [["Singapore Airlines", "ORG"]], "Florida Governor Ron DeSantis Botches COVID-19 Response - By banning Corona beer in order to flatten pandemic curve.": [["Florida", "GPE"], ["Ron DeSantis", "PERSON"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["Corona", "PRODUCT"]], "We apologise to the Government of Ekiti State for this error. We remain committed to improving our quality control processes to ensure accurate and transparent reporting of cases https://t.co/c6yPex9khE": [["the Government of Ekiti State", "ORG"]], "NYT invented the video of a doctor fighting coronavirus in hospital.": [["NYT", "ORG"]], "In May we did not break 30k cases in a day. Today the South alone reported 32830. https://t.co/fGCEGi3o7V": [["May", "DATE"], ["30", "CARDINAL"], ["a day", "DATE"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["South", "LOC"], ["32830", "CARDINAL"]], "ALERT: Americans With Coronavirus Symptoms Are Being Asked To Cough Directly Onto President Trump": [["Americans", "NORP"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]], "We launched the #COVID19 Solidarity Response Fund which has so far mobilized $225+M from more than 563000 individuals companies &amp; philanthropies. In addition we mobilized $1+ billion from Member States &amp; other generous to support countries-@DrTedros https://t.co/xgPkPdvn0r": [["the #COVID19 Solidarity Response Fund", "ORG"], ["more than 563000", "CARDINAL"]], "Football player Cristiano Ronaldo turned all his hotels into hospitals to help coronavirus patients and is paying doctors and the staff.": [["Cristiano Ronaldo", "PERSON"]], "including that there will again be testing of asymptomatic workers involved in managed isolation and quarantine and airport and border staff. This is part of our wider surveillance measures and is expected to be operational in early July.": [["early July", "DATE"]], "I don't want to do a national lockdown again.' If #coronavirus continues to 'progress' in the UK the PM says the govt will have to take \"further measures\" but insists that he doesn't want a \"second national lockdown\". Read more here: https://t.co/OC6eR6H6lg https://t.co/NlcySrwbbn": [["#coronavirus", "ORG"], ["UK", "GPE"], ["PM", "ORG"]], "Our daily update is published. States reported 586k tests 28k cases and 224 deaths. https://t.co/bqjpy9W8qf": [["daily", "DATE"], ["States", "ORG"], ["586", "CARDINAL"], ["28", "CARDINAL"], ["224", "CARDINAL"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona New Recoveries in India have exceeded the New Cases for 5 consecutive days. #COVID19 https://t.co/IWV0Eym3HD": [["India", "GPE"], ["the New Cases", "EVENT"], ["5 consecutive days", "DATE"]], "The top 5 States with high Active Caseload are also the ones which are presently reporting a high level of recoveries. https://t.co/hOWhFx5wPe": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Active Caseload", "ORG"]], "There are currently 4927 people in managed isolation and quarantine. Our current effective capacity is 7126. This gives us an excess capacity of 2199. Over the next week we are projecting 3590 arrivals and 2699 departures from our facilities.": [["4927", "CARDINAL"], ["7126", "CARDINAL"], ["2199", "CARDINAL"], ["the next week", "DATE"], ["3590", "CARDINAL"], ["2699", "CARDINAL"]], "Schools are struggling to cope with a lack of #COVID19 tests - with new infections increasing since it became compulsory for pupils to return. But when should you get your child tested for the virus? Here's our explainer 👇": [], "Scientists at AstraZeneca complain their work on a coronavirus vaccine keeps being delayed by Noddy Holder ringing up to ask if it will be ready by Christmas https://t.co/2lmYzTnAPx": [["AstraZeneca", "ORG"], ["Noddy Holder", "PERSON"], ["Christmas", "DATE"]], "Masks can help prevent the spread of #COVID19 when they are widely used in public. When you wear a mask you can help protect those around you. When others wear one they can help protect people around them incl. you. https://t.co/jkWwZTfWSS #WearAMask #DoYourPart #WorldMaskWeek https://t.co/O7FckRf1ks": [], "132 new cases of #COVID19Nigeria; Lagos-52 Gombe-27 Plateau-17 Kwara-10 Enugu-9 Ogun-9 Katsina-3 Ekiti-2 Bauchi-1 Osun-1 Rivers-1 56388 confirmed 44337 discharged 1083 deaths https://t.co/Enpey5u7xh": [["132", "CARDINAL"], ["44337", "CARDINAL"], ["1083", "CARDINAL"]], "Did You Already Have Coronavirus? Here’s A Simple Test https://t.co/PNbf76rsFF": [], "RT @MoHFW_INDIA: #IndiaFightsCorona With high number of sustained recoveries India surges ahead with highest single day RECOVERY. Nearl…": [["IndiaFightsCorona", "GPE"], ["India", "GPE"]], "Italy has surrendered to the coronavirus pandemic as all the measures to control COVID-19 have been exhausted.": [["Italy", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], "President Trump Has Been Forced to Wear a Protective Medical Mask https://t.co/nrGTiXVrtV #donaldtrump #coronavirus #cia #fbi #iud": [["Trump", "PERSON"]], "RT @EllenCutch: Coronavirus misinformation is moving offline. A reddit user posted this flyer to the site and told us it had been delive…": [["Coronavirus", "PRODUCT"]], "Orwell not dead but living under a bridge (continued) https://t.co/kL3j4vYwWP #government #toiletpaper #georgeorwell #coronavirus": [["Orwell", "PERSON"]], "Residents of York are asked what they think of a new government rule which allows people in England who may have #COVID19 to be fined up to £10000 if they fail to self-isolate. To read more click here: https://t.co/pqD1I8xgam https://t.co/QPgh3xlDIo": [["York", "GPE"], ["England", "GPE"]], "Central government has given permission for schools to re-open.": [], "As of today there are a total of 1339 @ICMRDELHI approved labs for #COVID19 testing. These consist of 911 Govt &amp; 428 Pvt labs: https://t.co/j4tAvyIcKc #CovidTesting #COVID__19 #COVID #Covid_19 #COVIDー19 #COVID19India #COVIDUpdates #coronavirus #CoronaUpdates #CoronavirusIndia https://t.co/Q0IuKceIFX": [["today", "DATE"], ["1339", "CARDINAL"], ["@ICMRDELHI", "ORG"], ["911", "CARDINAL"], ["428", "CARDINAL"]], "The government has come under pressure over a lack of availability of #COVID19 tests. Read more here: https://t.co/lMM9qgEryL https://t.co/KjwsinY5s1": [], "Fewer kids are dying since the lockdown - A new white paper examines why.": [], "More than 15 million cases of #COVID19 have now been reported to WHO and almost 620000 deaths. Although all countries have been affected we continue to see intense transmission in a relatively small group of countries-@DrTedros": [["More than 15 million", "CARDINAL"], ["WHO", "ORG"], ["almost 620000", "CARDINAL"]], "Justin Trudeau Resigns Amidst Coronavirus Pandemic https://t.co/hKmcnbXSnB": [["Justin Trudeau", "PERSON"]], "George Soros is one of the people responsible for the new coronavirus born in a laboratory.": [["George Soros", "PERSON"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "@JohnKin17583856 The sensitivity of the test is definitely something specialists are talking about. I have not seen a real number but I also haven’t looked that hard because we’ve been doing other things.-@alexismadrigal": [], "Experts Call Out Claims That Cow Dung/Urine, Yoga, AYUSH Can Prevent Or Treat COVID-19": [], "The main mode of transmission of #Novel #Coronavirus is through droplets and it is possible that infected smokers may blow droplets carrying the virus when they exhale. Regardless of #COVID19 you should steer clear of second-hand smoke as it may cause various health problems. https://t.co/aF3bZRlEve": [], "An article claiming that \"Bill Gates' vaccine\" would modify human DNA.": [["Bill Gates'", "PERSON"]], "RT @Surgeon_General: #DYK: #Handwashing remains one of the best ways to prevent the spread of viruses like #COVID19. Here are 5️⃣ things to…": [["5️⃣", "CARDINAL"]], "According to the State Health Department #Haryana #COVID19 #RecoveryRate in #Gurugram is 86.7%: https://t.co/oZ9KCDajIJ #COVID19 #Covid_19 #COVIDー19 #CoronaUpdates #CoronavirusIndia #CoronaVirusUpdates #coronavirus #COVIDUpdates https://t.co/2Sp8yRRRWj": [["the State Health Department", "ORG"]], "Our daily update is published. Sundays and Mondays are when we tend to see the numbers dip—and we see that today. Still: 62k cases rising hospitalizations and a large jump in deaths over last Sunday’s holiday numbers. The 7-day average is now back over 700. https://t.co/5hdQFxQ2OJ": [["daily", "DATE"], ["Sundays", "DATE"], ["Mondays", "DATE"], ["today", "DATE"], ["62", "CARDINAL"], ["last Sunday", "DATE"], ["7-day", "DATE"], ["over 700", "CARDINAL"]], "Our total number of confirmed cases of COVID-19 is now 1431 which is the number we report to the World Health Organization.": [["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["1431", "DATE"], ["the World Health Organization", "ORG"]], "Brazailian parliament went to a hospital that should take in COVID19 patients and found it was empty.": [["Brazailian", "GPE"]], "Multiple posts shared thousands of times on Facebook Twitter and YouTube claim that salt is an effective remedy against the novel coronavirus.": [["thousands", "CARDINAL"], ["Facebook Twitter", "ORG"], ["YouTube", "ORG"]], "UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres says the #COVID19 pandemic has \"dramatically derailed\" sustainable development goals and has \"put into question\" progress that was being made on the eradication of poverty and hunger. Latest world news: https://t.co/CDN8pokUbF https://t.co/TFzPdfFyRC": [["UN", "ORG"], ["Antonio Guterres", "PERSON"]], "An Instagram post is claiming Covid-19 tests tainted with coronavirus have been in circulation for \"many months\".": [["Instagram", "ORG"], ["Covid-19", "PRODUCT"], ["\"many months", "DATE"]], "Across the 21 states who report them we tracked 4468 hospitalizations the bulk in New York. But Louisiana and Florida also have growing numbers of hospitalizations.": [["21", "CARDINAL"], ["4468", "CARDINAL"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["Louisiana", "GPE"], ["Florida", "GPE"]], "Philippines Senators Grace Poe and Risa Hontiveros have been silent over the coronavirus crisis but were very vocal about the closure of ABS-CBN.": [["Philippines", "GPE"], ["Grace Poe", "PERSON"], ["Risa Hontiveros", "PERSON"], ["ABS-CBN", "ORG"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona: India’s Total Recoveries continue to rise cross 32.5 lakh today 5 States contribute 60% of total cases 62% of active cases and 70% of total fatality reported in India #StaySafe #IndiaWillWin https://t.co/KRn3GOaBNp": [["India", "GPE"], ["5", "CARDINAL"], ["India", "GPE"]], "\"The most important consequence of seeing COVID-19\nas a syndemic is to underline its social origins. The\nvulnerability of older citizens; Black, Asian, and minority\nethnic communities; and key workers who are commonly\npoorly paid with fewer welfare protections...\"": [["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["Black", "NORP"], ["Asian", "NORP"]], "RT @COVIDNewsByMIB: #IndiaFightsCorona: @ICMRDELHI scales up Covid-19 testing capacity to 3 lakh tests per day in country. As of now tota…": [["Covid-19", "ORG"]], "A video shows an Italian doctor who says that nobody died from coronavirus in Italy that it's not more dangerous than a flu.": [["Italian", "NORP"], ["Italy", "GPE"]], "Seasonal influenza vaccination will be mandatory in Georgia this fall. COVID-19 mortality rates are significantly lower than the fatalities caused by other viruses.": [["Georgia", "GPE"], ["this fall", "DATE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"]], "We can now say there are 33 cases in the Mt Roskill Evangelical Fellowship group and 13 cases in the bereavement sub-cluster which includes the cases whose source of infection was the bereavement events.": [["33", "CARDINAL"], ["Mt Roskill Evangelical Fellowship", "ORG"], ["13", "CARDINAL"]], "There is no one in New Zealand receiving hospital-level care for COVID-19.⁣ ⁣ Yesterday our laboratories completed 2111 tests bringing the total number of tests completed to date to 280983. #covid19 #covid19nz #COVIDー19": [["New Zealand", "GPE"], ["Yesterday", "DATE"], ["2111", "CARDINAL"], ["280983", "CARDINAL"]], "As at 11:50 pm 19th April the breakdown of cases by state is: Lagos- 376 FCT- 88 Kano- 36 Osun- 20 Oyo- 16 Edo- 15 Ogun- 12 Kwara- 9 Katsina- 12 Bauchi- 7 Kaduna- 6 Akwa Ibom- 9 Delta- 4 Ekiti- 3 Ondo- 3 Enugu- 2 Rivers-2 Niger- 2 Benue- 1 Anambra- 1 Borno- 1 Jigawa- 2": [], "The biggest change in the data is in the number of COVID-19 patients who are currently hospitalized. With the addition of Florida's 7k hospitalizations we’re now over 51000. We have not seen those numbers since the first week of May—and they do not seem likely to decline soon. https://t.co/tRvO4ypKGF": [["COVID-19", "CARDINAL"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["51000", "CARDINAL"], ["the first week of May", "DATE"]], "📢#CoronaVirusUpdates: 📍#COVID19 India Tracker (As on 7 September 2020 08:00 AM) ➡️Confirmed cases: 4204613 ➡️Recovered: 3250429 (77.3%)👍 ➡️Active cases: 882542 (21.0%) ➡️Deaths: 71642 (1.7%) #IndiaFightsCorona #IndiaWillWin #StaySafe Via @MoHFW_INDIA https://t.co/WVQslxqBPC": [["📍#COVID19 India Tracker", "ORG"], ["7 September 2020", "DATE"], ["4204613", "CARDINAL"], ["71642", "CARDINAL"]], "There is a person with coronavirus in Galicia on 2/4/20.": [["Galicia", "GPE"], ["2/4/20", "DATE"]], "India has now tested more than 2 lakh samples/day for #COVID19! This has been enabled by @ICMRDelhi's commitment to set up over 1000 Laboratories and expanding testing mechanisms. For details visit: https://t.co/FQhg5M5xrN #ICMRFightsCOVID19 #IndiaFightsCorona @MoHFW_INDIA https://t.co/rDkcvFbhUS": [["India", "GPE"], ["@ICMRDelhi", "ORG"], ["over 1000", "CARDINAL"], ["Laboratories", "ORG"]], "Claim that the Jordanian Health minister says COVID-19 is a conspiracy in a video.": [["Jordanian", "NORP"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], "Pregnant women with COVID have a 25% higher rate of premature births. https://t.co/g1hScYwGpr": [], "@WHO Solidarity Trials are also underway in many countries. Once these projects are complete controlling #COVID19 effectively will be easier due to the availability of proper medicines vaccines etc. as did to control various infectious diseases across the world.": [["@WHO Solidarity Trials", "EVENT"]], "COVID-19 update: There are no new cases of COVID-19 to report in New Zealand today. It has been 99 days since the last case of COVID-19 was acquired locally from an unknown source.": [["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["New Zealand", "GPE"], ["today", "DATE"], ["99 days", "DATE"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"]], "Compare the number of completed tests reported by New Mexico a state with a population 19 times smaller than California’s. These numbers should not even be close and yet they are. https://t.co/tzB9fZM6FP": [["New Mexico", "GPE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["California’s", "NORP"]], "All 12 cases in the community are Auckland based. All are connected to the existing outbreak as close contacts of cases already reported. 2 of the new cases are household contacts of a previously reported case that is still under investigation - the GP from Mt Wellington.": [["12", "CARDINAL"], ["Auckland", "GPE"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Mt Wellington", "GPE"]], "A precautionary message that one can catch fire due to hand sanitizer as it has a high amount of alcohol. The message also shows the hands of a lady who after applying sanitizer went near the stove and ended up burning her hands.": [], "That brings New Zealand’s total number of active cases to 14 all are in managed isolation or quarantine facilities. There are no cases in the community.  NZ's total number of confirmed cases of COVID-19 is now 1170 which is the number we report to the WHO.": [["New Zealand", "GPE"], ["14", "CARDINAL"], ["NZ", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["1170", "CARDINAL"], ["WHO", "ORG"]], "Says Rudy Giuliani \"bought $2M in shares of Novartis, a primary supplier of hydroxychloroquine\" in early February.": [["Rudy Giuliani", "PERSON"], ["Novartis", "ORG"], ["early February", "DATE"]], "_A student from Pondicherry University in India has found a home remedy for COVID-19 that has been accepted by World Health Organization (WHO)._": [["Pondicherry University", "ORG"], ["India", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["World Health Organization", "ORG"], ["WHO", "ORG"]], "Footballer Ronaldo is turning his hotels into COVID-19 hospitals.": [["Ronaldo", "PERSON"], ["19", "CARDINAL"]], "#CoronaVirusUpdates India records Highest ever single day peak of 63631 #COVID19 recoveries. #IndiaFightsCorona as Total recoveries cross 22 lakh. Recoveries exceed the active cases by more than 15 lakh. https://t.co/XBY3Er8K0P https://t.co/VDQSv7xVUB": [["India", "GPE"], ["single day", "DATE"], ["63631", "DATE"], ["22", "CARDINAL"], ["more than 15", "CARDINAL"]], "Do you have a cough fever or runny nose? If these symptoms came on suddenly there’s a good chance you could have #flu. Watch to find out what you should do next to #fightflu. https://t.co/fp3aSjumw4": [], "President Trump Says Pandas Are Responsible For Covid-19 https://t.co/mgan5G2oY8 #donaldtrump #china #coronavirus #zoo #pandas": [["Trump", "PERSON"]], "As of today there are 23917 active #COVID19 cases in #Mumbai District #Maharastra: https://t.co/6CcqIYgbXL @MoHFW_INDIA @drharshvardhan @DrHVoffice @MantralayaRoom #COVID__19 #Covid_19 #COVIDー19 #CoronaUpdatesInIndia #Coronavirus #CoronaVirusUpdates #CoronavirusPandemic https://t.co/k6ICon5kZ6": [["today", "DATE"], ["23917", "CARDINAL"], ["Mumbai", "GPE"]], "Public Health England's weekly #coronavirus report shows a rise of almost 23% in rhinovirus infections which include the common cold in the last week https://t.co/N6jzZYU7lJ": [["Public Health England's", "ORG"], ["weekly", "DATE"], ["the last week", "DATE"]], "This is an image of a suspected coronavirus vaccine causing COVID-19.": [], "Some people are more likely than others to become severely ill from #COVID19 which means that they may require hospitalization intensive care or a ventilator to help them breathe. Some severely ill people may die. Learn more. https://t.co/15lxFaQqX7 https://t.co/MAnreCAV8G": [], "Camila Pitanga Brazilian actress contracted COVID-19 but said she caught malaria so she could take chloroquine without admitting she was wrong.": [["Camila Pitanga", "PERSON"], ["Brazilian", "NORP"], ["COVID-19", "PERSON"]], "The new coronavirus \"causes sudden death syndrome.\"": [], "#IndiaFightsCorona: 📍 Increasing gap between #COVID19 Recovered &amp; Active cases of India (May 04 2020 to September 11 2020)👇 #StaySafe #IndiaWillWin https://t.co/FFJ4DKyspR": [["India", "GPE"], ["May 04 2020 to September 11 2020", "DATE"]], "Coronavirus parties can have deadly consequences. https://t.co/WTriJWJu9T": [], "Cabinet Office Minister Michael Gove says 'there's going to be a shift of emphasis' on working from home in the new #COVID19 restrictions. #KayBurley Get the latest #coronavirus news: https://t.co/hk8hrup8AY https://t.co/q8Btm4YE1P": [["Cabinet Office", "ORG"], ["Michael", "PERSON"], ["Gove", "PERSON"]], "@James_Gross Well they are now reporting quite effectively. It's just they refuse to put their numbers in a table or dashboard for reasons that are beyond me.": [["James_Gross", "PERSON"]], "Looking at the numbers this is not like yesterday where one state (California) drove a huge increase. This number seems much more solid driven by a number of states reporting large numbers of tests completed.": [["yesterday", "DATE"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["California", "GPE"]], "India has lost over 50000 individuals to coronavirus till date. In view of the rising coronavirus cases Bihar government extends lockdown in the state till 6 September. At Nationalist Congress Party chief Sharad Pawar’s residence four people tested positive for #coronavirus. https://t.co/LqGJHHVr2g": [["India", "GPE"], ["50000", "CARDINAL"], ["Bihar", "GPE"], ["6 September", "DATE"], ["Nationalist Congress Party", "ORG"], ["Sharad Pawar", "PERSON"], ["four", "CARDINAL"]], "Bill Gates profits from vaccination and wants to reduce the world's population.": [["Bill Gates", "PERSON"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona: @MoHFW_INDIA held a virtual meeting today with States &amp; UTs to ensure adequate Oxygen availability in all healthcare facilities &amp; unrestricted intra as well as inter State movement of oxygen. Read Details: https://t.co/cFx0MYEcFx #StaySafe #IndiaWillWin https://t.co/6jA2u1eY9Z": [["#IndiaFightsCorona: @MoHFW_INDIA", "ORG"], ["today", "DATE"], ["States", "GPE"], ["UTs", "ORG"]], "#HCPs: Attend the next COCA call Tuesday Aug 4 at 2pm ET via Zoom. Topic: COVID-19 &amp; Telehealth Implementation: Stories from the Field. Learn more: https://t.co/vWVKebacNF. #COVID19 https://t.co/yID3bDxiaP": [["COCA", "ORG"], ["Tuesday Aug 4", "DATE"], ["COVID-19 &amp", "ORG"]], "How a healthy 16-year-old boy lost his life to #COVID19 in just 12 days. https://t.co/smQHSWqt56": [["16-year-old", "DATE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["12 days", "DATE"]], "An important part of our work is data collection and analysis At 11:30pm every day our data Team collates results received from all testing laboratories to inform Nigerians of the number of new #COVID19 cases Results not received at this time are reported the next day https://t.co/Nyo6NeImRk": [["Nigerians", "NORP"], ["the next day", "DATE"]], "Finally we launched the first real version of the COVID Racial Data Tracker in partnership with @DrIbram and the @AntiracismCtr. This has been a major effort by our project's volunteers—and we hope it will be useful to communities across the country. https://t.co/hTyV0MA5tA": [["the COVID Racial Data Tracker", "ORG"], ["DrIbram", "ORG"], ["@AntiracismCtr", "PRODUCT"]], "Acc to @MoHFW_INDIA #Incubation period for #COVID19 which is the time between exposure to the novel #coronavirus (becoming infected) and symptom onset is 1 to 12.5 days (with median estimates of 5 to 6 days) but can be as long as 14 days. #Coronavirus #Covid_19 #COVIDー19 https://t.co/u0wkfQS3sM": [["1 to 12.5 days", "DATE"], ["5 to 6 days", "DATE"], ["as long as 14 days", "DATE"]], "Nasal flu vaccine side effects do not cause covid": [], "• Today’s cases bring our combined total of confirmed and probable COVID-19 cases to 1492.⁣ ⁣ • We now have 1368 people reported as having recovered. ⁣ • Today there are two people in hospital – one each in Middlemore and North Shore hospitals. Neither are in ICU.⁣": [["Today", "DATE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["1492", "CARDINAL"], ["1368", "CARDINAL"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Middlemore", "GPE"], ["North Shore", "LOC"], ["ICU", "ORG"]], "NEW PUBLICATION ➡️#COVID19 pandemic could cause #HIV treatment interruptions and allow an increase in new infections ➡️Programs should plan now to avoid these risks and save lives 🔰Full report https://t.co/0X4XeY1iIz Authors: @brittajewell JenniferSmith TimothyHallett https://t.co/mmRowJy5JR": [], "Transparency from our leaders is vital during this crisis. We must all have access to data so that we can make informed decisions about our own behavior changes. AZ residents you can access our data model projections at https://t.co/0u4iUx0kml https://t.co/rpkjdMZKeV": [["AZ", "GPE"]], "There is no one in NZ receiving hospital level care for COVID-19. ​ ​ Yesterday our laboratories completed 2575 tests bringing the total number of tests completed to 424719. The Minister is advised &amp; reassured that these numbers will continue to increase over the coming days.": [["NZ", "GPE"], ["Yesterday", "DATE"], ["2575", "CARDINAL"], ["424719", "CARDINAL"], ["the coming days", "DATE"]], "In @followlasg our rapid response team is working with NFELTP to strengthen community testing for #COVID19 in LGAs. The team provides support to newly reactivated LGA walk-in testing sites for increased testing capacity access and awareness of #COVID19 at the grassroot level. https://t.co/MnIu3OBT3v": [["@followlasg", "ORG"], ["NFELTP", "ORG"], ["LGAs", "ORG"]], "Of the new recovered cases about 60% are reported from five States viz. Maharashtra Tamil Nadu Andhra Pradesh Karnataka &amp; Uttar Pradesh. Maharashtra has alone contributed more than 22000 (23%) &amp; Andhra Pradesh has contributed more than 11000 (12.3%) to the new recoveries. https://t.co/NtODWIpFlp": [["five", "CARDINAL"], ["States", "GPE"], ["Maharashtra", "GPE"], ["Andhra Pradesh", "GPE"], ["Karnataka &amp", "GPE"], ["Uttar Pradesh", "GPE"], ["Maharashtra", "GPE"], ["22000", "CARDINAL"], ["Andhra Pradesh", "GPE"]], "Claim: India began screening passengers from #COVID19-affected countries before it had a single case: PM Modi Fact: The govt mandated universal screening of all internat'l flights only on March 4 by when 27 cases had been detected across 5 Indian states https://t.co/2cAogF5glZ": [["India", "GPE"], ["March 4", "DATE"], ["27", "CARDINAL"], ["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Indian", "NORP"]], "Says the coronavirus is ???a MILITARY BIO-WEAPON Developed by China's Army.??�": [["China", "GPE"], ["Army", "ORG"]], "In Indore India Police and doctors are injecting coronavirus positive blood in Muslims.": [["Indore India Police", "ORG"], ["Muslims", "NORP"]], "_Photo of a vaccine developed by U.S. scientists for COVID-19._": [["U.S.", "GPE"]], "A video clip shows a doctor couple who died after treating 134 COVID-19 patients.": [["134", "CARDINAL"], ["19", "CARDINAL"]], "1651 deaths were reported bringing the total in our dataset to 60710. This does not include 5126 probable COVID-19 deaths reported by NYC but not by New York State. We're working on separate accounting of lab-confirmed and probable deaths for all states where we can do so. https://t.co/J7rBzYS4RZ": [["1651", "CARDINAL"], ["60710", "CARDINAL"], ["5126", "CARDINAL"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["NYC", "GPE"], ["New York State", "GPE"]], "Youth sports organizations: As you resume activities have you planned what to do if a player visitor or coach gets sick with #COVID19? CDC offers tips to protect the health and safety of staff players and visitors involved in youth sports. Tips here: https://t.co/tnPX5fnVG6. https://t.co/opS9MqsKVF": [["CDC", "ORG"]], "Not one politician has died from the virus.": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona Health Ministry reviews COVID Management &amp; Response in 15 districts across 5 States exhibiting high caseload and fatality.": [["#IndiaFightsCorona Health Ministry", "ORG"], ["COVID Management", "ORG"], ["15", "CARDINAL"], ["5", "CARDINAL"], ["States", "GPE"]], "Where Are They Now: Covid-19 https://t.co/j6AAcjvhg9": [], "Leaked Report Says There Are 'Too Many Humans' On The Planet https://t.co/03kvl3oOXU #globalwarming #coronavirus #conspiracy": [], "Another current known data problem is Washington State. After rock-solid reporting through the early part of the outbreak their system got gummed up and we have not seen a new update from the state for days.": [["Washington State", "GPE"]], "India spraying pesticides at night to prevent COVID-19.": [["India", "GPE"]], "Home Ministry Has Declared That Posting On Coronavirus Has Been Declared A Punishable Offense": [], "If you refuse to #SocialDistance you should sign a pledge to bypass care if you get ill with #coronavirus. https://t.co/6bPYWerUwv via @ArthurCaplan https://t.co/NWYBleKp6a": [], "RT @CDCEnvironment: DO NOT use bleach solutions or other disinfecting products on food. Currently no cases of #COVID19 have been identifie…": [], "Free Coronavirus Test Kits Available To All https://t.co/vvmMt2AyAi #health #coronavirus": [], "@drharshvardhan dispels doubts raised over failure of one vaccine in clinical trials says trials are continuing only after expert committee reappraisal. “No significant mutation in SARS-CoV-2 in India”. “ICMR is actively exploring saliva-based test for COVID-19”. @PIB_India": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["India", "GPE"], ["ICMR", "ORG"]], "Thirty-nine GPs and specialists have written to the BMJ calling for action on long COVID. https://t.co/4Y5kGv3pF3 https://t.co/jTc1OucOmw": [["Thirty-nine", "CARDINAL"], ["BMJ", "ORG"]], "Scientists are expressing cautious optimism that a COVID-19 vaccine can be ready to go by the late spring of 2021 although it’s unclear how much longer it would take to distribute the vaccine widely. https://t.co/srNfKUra8c": [["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["the late spring of 2021", "DATE"]], "If you want more context about the hospitalization data situation check out our weekly roundup in which we tackled this transitional period and how it's producing erratic artificially deflated hospitalization data. https://t.co/TUohxwun8U https://t.co/cddxgJRrw1": [["weekly", "DATE"]], "#CoronaVirusUpdates: #COVID19 testing status update: @ICMRDELHI stated that 57239428 samples tested upto September 13 2020 978500 sample tested on September 13 2020 #StaySafe #IndiaWillWin https://t.co/awNpnMp4jv": [["September 13 2020 978500", "DATE"], ["September 13 2020", "DATE"]], "Video shows the first infected patient of COVID-19 at Dhanbad Hospital.": [["COVID-19", "ORG"], ["Dhanbad Hospital", "FAC"]], "Says Daniel Radcliffe has the coronavirus.": [["Daniel Radcliffe", "PERSON"]], "As of today there are a total of 331146 active #COVID19 cases in India and 246216 samples were tested today (till 6PM) for #COVID__19 #Lakshadweep has not reported a single case till date &amp; #ArunachalPradesh &amp; #Mizoram have not reported any #COVID_19 case in the last 24hrs https://t.co/7lq9UGEq9i": [["today", "DATE"], ["331146", "CARDINAL"], ["India", "GPE"], ["246216", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["Lakshadweep", "PRODUCT"], ["Mizoram", "GPE"]], "Trump And Coronavirus May End November 3rd https://t.co/Nn7tfMvxr3 #dranthonyfauci #smallpox": [["May End", "DATE"], ["November 3rd", "DATE"]], "#coronavirus This is how scientists believe #coronavirus affects the body. https://t.co/mLmhAN3TJf": [], "Former Rep. Trey Gowdy wrote essay past on social media claiming the COVID-19 pandemic was planned to help Democrats in the 2020 election.": [["Trey Gowdy", "PERSON"], ["COVID-19", "EVENT"], ["Democrats", "NORP"], ["2020", "DATE"]], "Health equity is when everyone has the opportunity to be as healthy as possible. We must address long-standing inequities that put some racial and ethnic groups at a higher risk for #COVID19. Learn about CDC’s COVID-19 #HealthEquity Strategy: https://t.co/OVro238b8r. https://t.co/XhT7GSFsGY": [["CDC", "ORG"]], "Product pages on @amazon are offering toxic chlorine dioxide, an industrial bleach often sold under the name “Miracle Mineral Solution” as a #covid19 cure. Reported by @edpilkington in the Guardian https://t.co/IIwGfF4hBe": [["Miracle Mineral Solution”", "PRODUCT"], ["@edpilkington", "ORG"], ["Guardian", "ORG"]], "The most recent date that we have confirmed data for North Carolina is May 16th. The Infection Rate was 1.11 meaning that COVID cases were slowly increasing.": [["North Carolina", "GPE"], ["May 16th", "DATE"], ["1.11", "CARDINAL"], ["COVID", "ORG"]], "It's possible that some vaccine could be available at the end of the year. CSA Patrick Vallance says a vaccine could be available in \"small amounts for certain groups\" adding that we're 'more likely to see vaccines over the first half of next year.' https://t.co/N2tOTQ6zuh https://t.co/PZLzrn3EGo": [["the end of the year", "DATE"], ["CSA Patrick Vallance", "ORG"], ["the first half of next year", "DATE"]], "In phase 1 doses will be allocated proportionally to all participating countries simultaneously to reduce overall risk. In phase 2 consideration will be given to countries’ in relation to threat and vulnerability-@DrTedros #COVID19 https://t.co/1KOCC24gcX": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "Great news! #Carona virus vaccine ready. Able to cure patient within 3 hours after injection. Hats off to US Scientists.\n\nRight now Trump announced that Roche Medical Company will launch the \nvaccine next Sunday, and millions of doses are ready from it !!! Note : \nThis message requires confirmation": [["Carona", "PRODUCT"], ["US", "GPE"], ["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Roche Medical Company", "ORG"], ["next Sunday", "DATE"], ["millions", "CARDINAL"]], "States reported 695 deaths. The trend here has been good. https://t.co/3YduwNHFWy": [["695", "CARDINAL"]], "176 new cases of #COVID19; 95-Lagos 31-Oyo 11-FCT 8-Niger 8-Borno 6-Jigawa 4-Kaduna 3-Anambra 2-Edo 2-Rivers 2-Nasarawa 2-Bauchi 1-Benue 1-Zamfara 5621 cases of #COVID19 in Nigeria Discharged: 1472 Deaths: 176 https://t.co/VBFAS6YQYJ": [["176", "CARDINAL"], ["Zamfara", "GPE"], ["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["1472", "CARDINAL"], ["176", "CARDINAL"]], "Twofold increase in mortality among coronavirus patients with #hypertension. https://t.co/ENlBNtdZbL": [], "As of July 6: In the last 7 days 9 states have reported more than 10000 new #COVID19 cases. Wear cloth face coverings keep 6ft+ between yourself and others and wash your hands often. Interested in data from your state? See the COVID Data Tracker: https://t.co/4Ku7nKLZCq https://t.co/HMPsgMSgrl": [["July 6", "DATE"], ["the last 7 days", "DATE"], ["9", "CARDINAL"], ["more than 10000", "CARDINAL"]], "???Covid is never going away! This is the beach today in Raleigh, North Carolina.??�": [["Covid", "PERSON"], ["today", "DATE"], ["Raleigh", "GPE"], ["North Carolina", "GPE"]], "Pope Francis Dying Of The Coronavirus? https://t.co/WjInjKYi4a": [], "290 new cases of #COVID19Nigeria; Lagos-82 Plateau-82 Oyo-19 FCT-18 Edo-16 Kaduna-15 Enugu-9 Ogun-9 Kano-8 Kwara-8 Cross River-5 Ondo-5 Rivers-5 Ekiti-4 Imo-3 Borno-2 46867 confirmed 33346 discharged 950 deaths https://t.co/d5sjk0gRls": [["290", "CARDINAL"], ["33346", "CARDINAL"], ["950", "CARDINAL"]], "People are offering prayers in groups on rooftops despite lockdown. That too when cases of coronavirus in India are continuously increasing.": [["India", "GPE"]], "The Access to #COVID19 Tools (ACT) Accelerator aims to provide equitable access to tools to tackle all forms of #COVID19 disease (from asymptomatic to mild and severe disease). https://t.co/zpL51DmyIy": [], "The positive rate has fallen a lot since early April. Back then it was ~20%. Now it's more like 4-5-6%. A lot of that change has been driven by the rising tests and plummeting positive rates in the northeast. https://t.co/9KrVY2od6X": [["early April", "DATE"]], "RT @imperialcollege: The UK government just announced £22.5 million to support Prof Robin Shattock’s @roboskis team’s phase two trials of a…": [["RT @imperialcollege", "ORG"], ["UK", "GPE"], ["Robin Shattock", "PERSON"], ["@roboskis", "PERSON"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "There are 1000 open vacancies for nurses doctors and other health professionals to work on a temporary hospital in São Paulo which will be used to treat COVID-19 cases.": [["1000", "CARDINAL"], ["São Paulo", "GPE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"]], "A photo from the funeral of a recently deceased Sri Lankan politician Arumugam Thondaman has been shared thousands of times in multiple Facebook posts. The posts claim the image shows one of Thondaman’s daughters violated Sri Lanka's mandatory coronavirus quarantine policy for travelers by attending the ceremony shortly after returning to the country from overseas.": [["Sri Lankan", "NORP"], ["Arumugam Thondaman", "PERSON"], ["thousands", "CARDINAL"], ["Facebook", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Thondaman", "PERSON"], ["Sri Lanka's", "GPE"]], "As of this morning we have identified 28 close contacts of the Tokoroa health professional currently in the hospital for COVID-19. 16 of those have already been contacted. We expect to contact the remainder today.": [["28", "CARDINAL"], ["Tokoroa", "NORP"], ["16", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"]], "The last places free of #COVID19 are in the Pacific. Here’s how WHO helped countries in the region step up their efforts to prepare for the arrival of COVID-19👉https://t.co/jgwGoj6z8b #WHOImpact https://t.co/xsBv8DwGxS": [["#COVID19", "FAC"], ["Pacific", "LOC"], ["WHO", "ORG"]], "New COVIDView reports hospitalization rates and deaths from #COVID19 are increasing. Indicators that track hospitalizations and deaths usually lag behind indicators that track illness. https://t.co/zP4VYlo0Pb https://t.co/wPTwIVFQF5": [["New COVIDView", "ORG"]], "While it is true that coronavirus can cause a sore throat and gargling with salt and warm water may make it feel better, it has no direct effect on the virus. #COVID19 #afaracare": [], "A DNA vaccine* has been shown to work in rhesus monkeys; after exposing the vaccinated monkeys to COVID they had less virus in their lungs. Read the study from @ScienceMagazine --&gt; https://t.co/lr8f3qmP5v": [], "10 important strategies for dealing with the doomsday scenario of #COVID flu and measles. https://t.co/S4dscsM7XX https://t.co/Nb1o1D0RNs": [["10", "CARDINAL"]], "Older children seem to spread COVID like adults. https://t.co/Sd5peyONOo https://t.co/6ejMr1X9F5": [], "We’re grateful for the support from @IHSTowers in providing 4 ambulances for Nigeria’s #COVID19 response These will be used by Port Health Services of @Fmohnigeria; Kano Edo &amp; Oyo State Emergency Operations Centres to expand the current capacity for transportation of cases https://t.co/cZuNClL63o": [["@IHSTowers", "ORG"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["Port Health Services", "ORG"], ["Fmohnigeria", "GPE"], ["Kano Edo", "GPE"], ["Oyo State Emergency Operations Centres", "ORG"]], "Sadly there are 4 people in hospital today around the country with COVID-19. two are in a ward at North Shore Hospital two are in ICU one at North Shore and one at Waikato hospital. We are hoping for everyone’s full and speedy recovery.": [["4", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["North Shore Hospital", "FAC"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["ICU", "GPE"], ["North Shore", "LOC"], ["Waikato", "GPE"]], "Indian politician Uddhav Thackeray has asked Christians to pray to Jesus to stop COVID-19.": [["Indian", "NORP"], ["Uddhav Thackeray", "PERSON"], ["Christians", "NORP"], ["Jesus", "PERSON"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], "The average number of cases nationwide has flattened over the past week breaking the downward trend we had seen in the beginning of August. https://t.co/S95tiOEcwN": [["the past week", "DATE"], ["the beginning of August", "DATE"]], "There are 59 positive coronavirus cases in Nagpur along with three doctors one of whom is on ventilator.": [["59", "CARDINAL"], ["Nagpur", "GPE"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "The latest CDC #COVIDView report shows that minority populations like American Indian Black and Hispanic continue to be hospitalized for #COVID19 at nearly 5 times the rate of their non-Hispanic White counterparts. Learn more: https://t.co/zP4VYlo0Pb. https://t.co/hpMlWPxD25": [["CDC #COVIDView", "ORG"], ["American Indian Black", "NORP"], ["Hispanic", "NORP"], ["nearly 5", "CARDINAL"]], "@AsxGold Kia ora Only New Zealand residents and citizens (and their children and partners) are permitted to enter New Zealand.": [["New Zealand", "GPE"], ["New Zealand", "GPE"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona TEST TRACK TREAT- effective implementation by the Centre and States/UTs has ensured that India has one of lowest #COVID19 cases and deaths per million population compared to several other countries. https://t.co/Caqhv0M0rK": [["the Centre and States/UTs", "ORG"], ["India", "GPE"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["million", "CARDINAL"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona Union Health Ministry urges States/UTs to ensure that no restriction is imposed on the movement of Medical Oxygen between States. https://t.co/6Yx9XzSUZT @PMOIndia @drharshvardhan @AshwiniKChoubey @PIB_India @DDNewslive @airnewsalerts @ICMRDELHI @mygovindia": [["#IndiaFightsCorona Union Health Ministry", "ORG"], ["States/UTs", "ORG"], ["States", "GPE"]], "STUDY: COVID was likely in the mix of Seattle’s early 2020 flu season. https://t.co/t6s1HdB0MH": [["COVID", "ORG"], ["Seattle", "GPE"], ["early 2020 flu season", "DATE"]], "A photo shows people infected with coronavirus lying on the sidewalk in China.": [["China", "GPE"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona Active cases only 22% of total #COVID19 cases. Recoveries are now 26 lakh. Exceed Active cases by more than 18 lakh. https://t.co/ftuVx5TuRG https://t.co/0YVdlEOYBR": [["26 lakh", "DATE"], ["more than 18", "CARDINAL"]], "\"States like New York, Illinois and California have been vocal in their demands for funding to bail out their pension systems, which were failing long before the COVID-19 outbreak, and other programs that aren???t related to this crisis.\"": [["New York", "GPE"], ["Illinois", "GPE"], ["California", "GPE"], ["the COVID-19", "EVENT"]], "NEWS! Anti-vaxxers close to deciding which medical conditions they will pretend are caused by Coronavirus vaccine https://t.co/daWxNYpj86 https://t.co/eNvXR50ByR": [], "#CoronaVirusUpdates: 📍Total #COVID19 Cases in India (as on September 17 2020) ▶️78.64% Cured/Discharged/Migrated (4025079) ▶️19.73% Active cases (1009976) ▶️1.63% Deaths (83198) Total COVID-19 confirmed cases = Cured/Discharged/Migrated+Active cases+Deaths https://t.co/HUKbDQm35f": [["India", "GPE"], ["September 17 2020", "DATE"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"]], "328 new cases of #COVID19; Lagos-121 FCT-70 Bauchi-25 Rivers-18 Oyo-16 Kaduna-15 Gombe-14 Edo-13 Ogun-13 Jigawa-8 Enugu-6 Kano-5 Osun-2 Ondo-2 11844 cases of #COVID19Nigeria Discharged: 3696 Deaths: 333 https://t.co/XQ3B7O0yIb": [["328", "CARDINAL"]], "Florida's numbers today include a large number of backlogged tests the state said. https://t.co/esoLo6GPGN": [["Florida", "GPE"], ["today", "DATE"]], "Local lockdown measures are to be imposed in the Welsh county of Rhondda Cynon Taf after a rise in coronavirus cases https://t.co/ODij6cY0SG": [["Welsh", "NORP"], ["Rhondda Cynon Taf", "GPE"]], "WHO announces Algeria outside of danger regarding COVID-19.": [["WHO", "ORG"], ["Algeria", "GPE"]], "States reported nearly 27k cases today the most in more than 40 days (May 8). The positive rate was the highest since late May. https://t.co/LzR2w6HTvN": [["nearly 27", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["more than 40 days", "DATE"], ["May 8)", "DATE"], ["late May", "DATE"]], "The vast majority of students at St Dominic’s are casual contacts and being tested as a precaution. If these students and staff are well and have no symptoms of COVID-19 they do not need to self-isolate while waiting for test results.": [["St Dominic", "ORG"]], "Prime Minister Boris Johnson says the government will \"very shortly\" be setting out \"the priority of the groups that we think should have COVID tests\". Follow live updates as the PM faces questions from the liaison committee: https://t.co/MCYJ946KfV https://t.co/qlPstqmj0g": [["Boris Johnson", "PERSON"], ["COVID", "ORG"], ["PM", "ORG"]], "Antibodies for the common cold produce a positive COVID-19 test. False-positive results from COVID-19 antibody testing are behind the COVID-19 cases reported in the U.S.": [["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["U.S", "GPE"]], "Children under 18 years represent about 8.5% of reported #COVID19 cases with few deaths compared to other age groups &amp; usually mild disease. 👉 https://t.co/Cs7uxQRRMN https://t.co/l4gqfttYmg": [["under 18 years", "DATE"]], "Man beaten in Deoria India in lockdown time.": [["Deoria", "GPE"], ["India", "GPE"]], "Our daily update is published. We’ve now tracked 9.7 million tests up 306k from yesterday. Note that we can only track tests that a state reports. For details see: https://t.co/PZrmH4bl5Y https://t.co/DJDFYX4meY": [["daily", "DATE"], ["9.7 million", "CARDINAL"], ["yesterday", "DATE"]], "Coronavirus Is Not Like A Broken Leg https://t.co/gGjYVfJzRC": [], "Photos show masses fleeing Myanmar for Thailand due to coronavirus pandemic": [["Myanmar", "GPE"], ["Thailand", "GPE"]], "Georgia is particularly worrisome. The state had not seen a large rise in reported deaths despite rising infections and a steep hospitalization curve. Today the state reported its second-highest deaths since the beginning of the pandemic and the highest number since April 7. https://t.co/XUz1nnA1bl": [["Georgia", "GPE"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["April 7", "DATE"]], "New findings confirm earlier research showing a major increase in physician employment by hospitals over the past decade. https://t.co/WOOlRIgvKu": [["the past decade", "DATE"]], "Ireland's entire cabinet will \"restrict their movements\" after the health minister felt unwell and was tested for #coronavirus it has been reported https://t.co/i5zO9bFugY": [["Ireland", "GPE"]], "In the backdrop of the lockdown videos of wild animals taking over the roads are surfacing on the internet. Among them a set of pictures of a herd of deer is doing the rounds on social media claiming that these pictures are from Lake Club Chandigarh.": [["Lake Club Chandigarh", "FAC"]], "The reported death toll today is 1760 about the same as last Friday. Only two states reported over 200 deaths today (NY and PA). https://t.co/0EjueTbsWz": [["today", "DATE"], ["1760", "DATE"], ["last Friday", "DATE"], ["Only two", "CARDINAL"], ["over 200", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["NY", "GPE"], ["PA", "GPE"]], "One optimistic point: there are 15 states on the left side of this chart that are finding very few positive cases even if they're doing a lot of testing. This suggests their mitigation strategies are working. https://t.co/i9bbZKvMkC": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["15", "CARDINAL"]], "@MathGuy_7 @HedgeyeDJ Thank you - extremely insightful. Is there one or two trusted websites that you follow to provide a good summary &amp; update on covid? I follow @chrismartenson and he does a really good job. Recent video touted importance of Vitamin D and elderberry, among other things.": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "Florida broke New York’s 7-day average record for cases per million population today. Testing capacity is obviously much much greater now than in spring. However it’s still stunning to see that record fall. https://t.co/VGzrM6uWGW": [["Florida", "GPE"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["7-day", "DATE"], ["million", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["spring", "DATE"]], "As the outbreak continues many people in the United States will at some point in time either this year or next be exposed to #COVID19; it’s likely many will become sick but most people likely will have mild illness. https://t.co/SlDrVXXfCz": [["the United States", "GPE"], ["this year", "DATE"]], "Sir Ganga Ram Hospital has directed patients to stay at home n treat Urself. Implies Delhi Govt has miserably failed in its administrative responsibility of providing health care n left the Delhites to their fate. Must be sacked n LG take the charge. U agree?": [["Ganga Ram Hospital", "PERSON"], ["Urself", "PERSON"], ["Delhi Govt", "ORG"], ["Delhites", "NORP"], ["LG", "ORG"]], "One of the previously reported cases is now considered to have recovered. Our total number of active cases is 116. Of those 39 are imported cases in MIQ facilities and 77 are community cases. ​⁣⁣ ​⁣⁣ ​⁣⁣": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["116", "CARDINAL"], ["39", "CARDINAL"], ["MIQ", "ORG"], ["77", "CARDINAL"]], "Joe Diffie???s death was labeled ???as a COVID-19 death and it wasn???t!??�": [["Joe Diffie", "PERSON"]], "Modeling is all about assumptions. We assume a baseline general hospital occupancy rate of 60% across all hospitals accounting for hospitalized non-COVID patients. We assume that hospitals can increase their available beds for COVID patients by roughly double (207%).": [], "More than 1/3 of BAME doctors in the UK are still not being given access to potentially life-saving Covid-19 risk assessments. https://t.co/qsgKFqj5p4": [["More than 1/3", "CARDINAL"], ["BAME", "ORG"], ["UK", "GPE"], ["Covid-19", "LAW"]], "Our daily update is published. States reported 772k tests 47k cases and 1023 deaths. https://t.co/h7Ur4Y2f3t": [["daily", "DATE"], ["States", "ORG"], ["772", "CARDINAL"], ["47", "CARDINAL"], ["1023", "CARDINAL"]], "A doctor named Leslie Chow discovered the coronavirus and died after contact with coronavirus patients.": [["Leslie Chow", "PERSON"]], "Though the number of new cases has remained relatively flat the regional data shows that we're not in a steady state. Here are new cases by region scaled for population. https://t.co/VM8nPWHuKS": [], "Yesterday our labs processed 9257 tests. Our total number of tests completed to date is 719320.​ ​ There are 159 people linked to the community cluster at the Auckland quarantine facility. This includes 85 people who have tested positive and their household contacts.": [["Yesterday", "DATE"], ["9257", "CARDINAL"], ["719320", "CARDINAL"], ["159", "CARDINAL"], ["Auckland", "GPE"], ["85", "CARDINAL"]], "Coronavirus: Hospital in urgent plea for people not to go to 'very busy' A&amp;E for COVID-19 tests https://t.co/05NRugoqJS": [["A&amp", "FAC"]], "Rightmove said activity - aided by the current stamp duty holiday - was being driven by high demand for gardens and more space to work from home as #COVID19 disrupts day-to-day life https://t.co/ADgXpjblhl": [["Rightmove", "ORG"]], "Says \"there is no\" COVID-19 virus.": [], "Anyone on the flight or in the facility at the same time as the cases are being treated as if they are close contacts. They will all be tested and isolated until a negative result is received.": [], "@Chris_Fairchild We don’t do that because not all states provide negative results with the same frequency or comprehensiveness. At this point I don’t think positive rates are as important as other indicators. -@alexismadrigal": [["Chris_Fairchild", "PERSON"]], "437 new cases of #COVID19Nigeria; Lagos-107 FCT-91 Plateau-81 Kaduna-32 Ogun-30 Kwara-24 Ebonyi-19 Ekiti-17 Oyo-8 Borno-6 Edo-6 Kano-4 Nasarawa-3 Osun-3 Taraba-3 Gombe-2 Bauchi-1 46577 confirmed 33186 discharged 945 deaths https://t.co/d70c7hFaHc": [["437", "CARDINAL"], ["33186", "CARDINAL"], ["945", "CARDINAL"]], "As per #TamilNadu Govt a total of 86073 samples were tested for #COVID19 on 20 Sep 2020 #COVID__19 #COVID #COVID_19 #COVIDー19 #COVID19India #Corona #coronavirus #CoronavirusIndia #CoronavirusPandemic #CoronaVirusUpdates #CovidUpdates #CoronaUpdate #CoronaUpdatesIndia https://t.co/ozPOAHr3zS": [["86073", "CARDINAL"], ["20 Sep 2020", "DATE"]], "Trump’s effort to blame Obama for sluggish coronavirus testing.": [["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Obama", "PERSON"]], "First there’ll be some changes in how we track pending numbers so that state totals go up and down less erratically. Second we’ll be tracking more numbers from states and broaden our grading criteria. Third we’ll be making major changes to the website.": [], "#IndiaFightsCorona India climbs another historic peak of more than 13 lakh tests. More than 13.80 lakh tests done in the last 24 hours. @PMOIndia @drharshvardhan @AshwiniKChoubey @PIB_India @DDNewslive @airnewsalerts @ICMRDELHI @COVIDNewsByMIB @PTI_News @ANI": [["India", "GPE"], ["more than 13", "CARDINAL"]], "The states reported more than 21000 newly discovered cases today up from last week's low but almost an exact match for last Tuesday's new-case number. https://t.co/7LZNnGowAk": [["more than 21000", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["last week's", "DATE"], ["last Tuesday's", "DATE"]], "Public broadcast RTVE published a map of coronavirus cases in Spain that in fact was a map of penis' average size in different regions.": [["RTVE", "ORG"], ["Spain", "GPE"]], "Allegheny County (PA) Department of Emergency Services is using diverse sources for their response planning including Covid Act Now. https://t.co/hcVbHYvSmw https://t.co/Hd08bBPn3Q": [["Allegheny County", "GPE"], ["PA", "GPE"], ["Department of Emergency Services", "ORG"], ["Covid Act Now", "LAW"]], "In an Aaj Tak news report the Chinese prime minister said \"Reading Quran and offering namaz is the only cure for COVID-19.\"": [["Aaj Tak", "ORG"], ["Chinese", "NORP"]], "As of Aug. 31 national forecasts suggest new weekly #COVID19 deaths may decrease in the coming weeks with 3300 to 7500 new deaths during the week ending Sept. 26. Forecasts predict 200k to 211k total COVID-19 deaths in the US by Sept. 26. More: https://t.co/Ft6cgmaMPX. https://t.co/C1JhB3v5jg": [["Aug. 31", "DATE"], ["weekly", "DATE"], ["the coming weeks", "DATE"], ["3300", "CARDINAL"], ["7500", "CARDINAL"], ["the week ending Sept. 26", "DATE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["US", "GPE"], ["Sept.", "DATE"], ["26", "CARDINAL"]], "Developers, Banks Tell Government They've Already Spent Ireland's Share Of EU's €1 Trillion Covid Recovery Fund https://t.co/rJDMlwsjes": [["Ireland", "GPE"]], "@DrJudyAMikovits What promises that a viable vaccine can be developed for COVID-19 virus. So, i think they should rehire Judith Mikovits who is a living scientific encyclopedia on viral research. She was involved with the scientific research that permitted": [["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["Judith Mikovits", "PERSON"]], "Nancy Pelosi Suggests That The Coronavirus (C-19) Be Renamed The (C-45) in Honor of President Trump https://t.co/sj9al7BaWb #donaldtrump": [["Nancy Pelosi", "PERSON"], ["Trump", "PERSON"]], "RT @WHOAFRO: How children can wear a #mask safely!😷👇🏿 Children must clean their hands🧼👐🏿💧 and maintain a safe distance📏 to stop the spread…": [], "Mar-a-Lago Tests Positive For the Coronavirus https://t.co/d4Pkmc1CYG #donaldtrump #coronavirus #mikepence #maralago #kayleighmcenany": [], "Covid-19 vaccine by Oxford university a success, 72 people 'cured'": [["Covid-19", "ORG"], ["Oxford", "GPE"], ["72", "CARDINAL"]], "The confirmation earlier today of a second death linked to COVID-19 in the last two days means the number of COVID-19 related deaths in New Zealand is now 24.": [["COVID-19", "EVENT"], ["the last two days", "DATE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["New Zealand", "GPE"], ["24", "DATE"]], "This photo shows French nurses holding a sign to denounce police violence.": [["French", "NORP"]], "Our daily update is published. States reported 70k new cases of COVID-19 a solid 819k tests and 1529 COVID-19 deaths today. Our 7-day average for deaths is now over 1000. https://t.co/P0L4w8Y6oq": [["daily", "DATE"], ["States", "GPE"], ["70k", "CARDINAL"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["819", "CARDINAL"], ["1529", "CARDINAL"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["today", "DATE"], ["7-day", "DATE"], ["1000", "CARDINAL"]], "WHO warns against consuming cabbage to prevent COVID-19": [["WHO", "ORG"]], "#CoronaVirusUpdates: 📍Total #COVID19 Cases in India (as on September 22 2020) ▶️80.12% Cured/Discharged/Migrated (4497867) ▶️17.54% Active cases (975861) ▶️1.60% Deaths (88935) Total COVID-19 confirmed cases = Cured/Discharged/Migrated+Active cases+Deaths https://t.co/AGeRkG5eGm": [["India", "GPE"], ["September 22 2020", "DATE"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"]], "The weekend lag effect is pronounced in death reporting. For example last week CA reported 6 deaths on Monday then 111 on Tues. AZ reported 1 death Mon then 117 on Tues. Today AZ reported 8 deaths. CA 23. All these data are the outputs of complicated human processes. https://t.co/WkN4aqCiGT": [["weekend", "DATE"], ["last week", "DATE"], ["CA", "ORG"], ["6", "CARDINAL"], ["Monday", "DATE"], ["111", "CARDINAL"], ["Tues", "DATE"], ["AZ", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Mon", "PERSON"], ["117", "CARDINAL"], ["Tues", "DATE"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["AZ", "ORG"], ["8", "CARDINAL"], ["23", "CARDINAL"]], "Most of you know this by now but there is a very strong weekend effect that hits on Sundays and Mondays especially in the reporting of COVID-19 deaths. Sundays are highlighted in red below. https://t.co/fpaDhxolj0": [["weekend", "DATE"], ["Sundays", "DATE"], ["Mondays", "DATE"], ["COVID", "ORG"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["Sundays", "DATE"]], "With 10576 new infections Maharashtra records highest single-day spike in the state so far. Starting 2pm tomorrow Manipur to go under a complete lockdown for 14 days. Bhopal in Madhya Pradesh to impose a city-wide lockdown from July 24 to August 3. #COVID19 #coronavirusFacts https://t.co/6U1006Zp1P": [["10576", "CARDINAL"], ["Maharashtra", "GPE"], ["single-day", "DATE"], ["Manipur", "GPE"], ["14 days", "DATE"], ["Bhopal", "GPE"], ["Madhya Pradesh", "GPE"], ["July 24 to August 3", "DATE"]], "Louisiana has posted record case counts back-to-back after not reporting on Saturday. One positive thread: compare the hospitalizations to cases charts and it's clear we're diagnosing more infections. On 4/2 LA's first peak they did 5300 tests. Today 33620. https://t.co/rgmowepkFE": [["Louisiana", "GPE"], ["Saturday", "DATE"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["4/2", "CARDINAL"], ["LA", "GPE"], ["5300", "CARDINAL"], ["Today", "DATE"]], "A WhatsApp forward attributed to CNN claims Dr. Li Wenliang, the whistleblower of the Chinese government's propaganda about COVID-19, has documented a research report. According to this report, chemicals like Methylxanthine, Theobromine and Theophylline stimulate compounds that can ward off this virus in a human body with at least an average performing immune system.": [["WhatsApp", "ORG"], ["CNN", "ORG"], ["Li Wenliang", "PERSON"], ["Chinese", "NORP"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["Methylxanthine", "PRODUCT"], ["Theobromine", "PRODUCT"], ["Theophylline", "PRODUCT"]], "We're debunking misinformation about coronavirus. Why? Because hoaxes travel fast and the numbers and causes of this growing outbreak need clarification. https://t.co/LqLfuNenns https://t.co/1eUOMfkdKu": [], "More detail on this from one of @COVID19Tracking's sharpest observers @jordan_zino from @GavinNewsom's livestream. https://t.co/l2s3AloB28 https://t.co/oZuw8XckHd": [["@COVID19Tracking's", "ORG"], ["GavinNewsom", "ORG"]], "A person who has been released from quarantine or isolation does not pose a risk of spreading #COVID19 to other people. Share facts about #coronavirus disease 2019! https://t.co/2AfHZLQ83v https://t.co/sAwdcn4BpE": [["2019", "DATE"]], "The pandemic has opened up the door for physicians to online learning for physicians new Medscape report finds. https://t.co/jitKgkTrRT": [["Medscape", "ORG"]], "Young people \"have a greater chance of being killed by the HPV vaccine than COVID-19.”": [], "There is no pandemic": [], "A growing number of states and cities are requiring a face covering for anyone leaving their home. Learn more about the best materials to make your own face mask and how to properly wear and care for them: https://t.co/oSTj2oqq3m": [], "The latest CDC #COVIDView report shows that weekly hospitalizations associated with #COVID19 have peaked twice since the outbreak began once during the week ending April 18 and a second time during the week ending July 18. Learn more: https://t.co/zP4VYlo0Pb. https://t.co/N1XLuxr9Hw": [["CDC", "ORG"], ["weekly", "DATE"], ["the week ending April 18", "DATE"], ["the week ending July 18", "DATE"]], "Coronavirus was spread via bananas": [], "@VinLew Kia ora Vincent Sorry you're having issues with the app. Please call the Ministry of Health team on 0800 800 606 or email your query and/or feedback about the app to tracingapp-feedback@health.govt.nz.": [["VinLew Kia", "ORG"], ["Vincent", "PERSON"], ["the Ministry of Health", "ORG"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona Focused and effective efforts of containment testing isolation and treatment have resulted in increasing percentage recovery rates and steadily falling percentage active cases. https://t.co/GWHeeWBb9s": [], "Our total number of confirmed cases of COVID-19 is now 1442 which is the number we report to the World Health Organization. ​ ​ Yesterday our laboratories processed 8953 tests bringing the total number of tests completed to date to 848420.": [["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["1442", "DATE"], ["the World Health Organization", "ORG"], ["Yesterday", "DATE"], ["8953", "CARDINAL"], ["848420", "CARDINAL"]], "China president xi jinping visited masjid and request Muslims for dua in present crisis country going through.we need your help.": [["China", "GPE"], ["xi", "PERSON"], ["Muslims", "NORP"]], "In this video italian representative Sara Cunial tells the truth about Bill Gates and its will to control world population through vaccines and medical experiment.": [["Sara Cunial", "PERSON"], ["Bill Gates", "PERSON"]], "A message is circulating, claiming that Kins of those who died of COVID-19 can claim insurance under Pradhan Mantri Jeevan Jyoti Bima Yojana (PMJJBY) &amp; Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana (PMSBY). https://t.co/OjQHiBUECp": [["Kins", "PERSON"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["Pradhan Mantri Jeevan Jyoti Bima Yojana", "PERSON"], ["Pradhan Mantri Suraksha Bima Yojana", "PERSON"]], "Testing positive for antibodies to the virus that causes #COVID19 means you likely had a past infection. It’s not yet known whether antibodies will protect you from getting infected again. Learn more about antibody testing: https://t.co/Xa1qKwzJhO. https://t.co/SgRRNBVcG7": [], "RT @PIB_India: Recovered cases are 2.93 times the number of Active Cases. 1977779 people have been recovered so far. 673166 are activ…": [["2.93", "CARDINAL"], ["1977779", "CARDINAL"]], "At the same time bilateral vaccine deals and vaccine nationalism could compromise equitable access and hold up progress for all countries in bringing the #COVID19 pandemic to an end-@DrTedros": [], "Nevada \"quietly\" reversed its \"decision to block HCQ prescriptions for COVID-19.\"": [["Nevada", "GPE"], ["HCQ", "ORG"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"]], "#coronavirus #Covid19 or #NYC “If people saw this, they would stay home.HORRIBLE.#StayHome #StayAtHome #StaySafe #NYC #NYCLockdown #FridayFeeling https://t.co/UTKzUPNxIl": [["#NYC", "ORG"]], "@jsolomonReports Soon 67\nNever had flu vaccine, never had flu\nMost all I know who got flu vaccine also got flu\nThat’s 1st person knowledge, not conjecture\n\nAlt: Organic dk greens, protein, exercise, H2O, sodium bicarbonate, D3, C, iodine, etc\n\nJESUS is my physician\nGreatest ever was, is, will be": [["JESUS", "PERSON"]], "Just watch this video and remember that incident when Zomato's Deepinder made a big deal out of someone refusing a delivery from a Muslim guy. There have been so many incidents that you just can't trust them. Who wants to eat food contaminated with spit?": [["Zomato", "PERSON"], ["Deepinder", "PERSON"], ["Muslim", "NORP"]], "“For the World Health Organization the international entity whose sole responsibility it is to alert the world of global pandemics like this to miss this is a huge problem.”": [["the World Health Organization", "ORG"]], "RT @DrTedros: COVAX is a groundbreaking way to pool R&amp;D &amp; procurement risks across multiple vaccines. It enables countries to place collect…": [["COVAX", "ORG"], ["R&amp", "PRODUCT"]], "It puts the facemask on the skin, or it gets the lockdown again\n\nGet yours HERE &gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/UMG2Y6AF0k https://t.co/S7xZsWTKib": [], "Yesterday our laboratories completed 824 tests bringing the total completed to date to 311121 - lower testing volumes are regularly observed over weekends. Anyone with symptoms that could be COVID-19 should call Healthline their GP about getting a test - which is free.": [["Yesterday", "DATE"], ["824", "CARDINAL"], ["311121", "CARDINAL"], ["weekends", "DATE"], ["COVID-19", "LAW"], ["Healthline", "ORG"], ["GP", "ORG"]], "Our total number of confirmed cases to 1184 which is the number we report to the World Health Organization.": [["1184", "CARDINAL"], ["the World Health Organization", "ORG"]], "Madhya Pradesh is reimposing lockdown due to rise in COVID cases": [["Madhya Pradesh", "GPE"]], "The group of 2159: Aside from the people on compassionate exemptions all of these people had completed a full 14 days in managed isolation. A reminder to anyone who was in a managed isolation facility between June 9-16 who has not yet spoken with Healthline to call 093020408.": [["2159", "CARDINAL"], ["a full 14 days", "DATE"], ["June 9-16", "DATE"], ["Healthline", "ORG"]], "Healthcare workers are scared because too many people won’t wear a mask. https://t.co/5yto2C39oc": [], "Both of the cases were picked up at our routine testing at around day 3. One of the cases who has been in isolation in Wellington is now considered recovered.Recovered being at least 10 days since onset of symptoms at least 48 hours asymptomatic and has returned a negative test.": [["around day 3", "DATE"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Wellington", "GPE"], ["at least 10 days", "DATE"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona In its collaborative and determined fight against #COVID19 India has scaled a new peak. 66500 the highest number of patients have recovered and been discharged yesterday. https://t.co/8dFhF3pvPa": [["India", "GPE"], ["66500", "CARDINAL"], ["yesterday", "DATE"]], "The Simpsons predicted the new coronavirus outbreak.": [["Simpsons", "PERSON"]], "#SwasthaBharat National telemedicine service completes over 1.5 lakh consultations. https://t.co/sAJutQcAEW": [["1.5", "CARDINAL"]], "RT @PIB_India: Nearly 9 lakh (899864) tests have been conducted in a single day the highest tests/day so far: Secretary @MoHFW_INDIA at…": [["899864", "CARDINAL"], ["a single day", "DATE"], ["@MoHFW_INDIA", "PERSON"]], "Bollywood Actress Aishwarya Rai To Host A Coronavirus Telethon/Auction in Mumbai https://t.co/99dP2Q8LKQ #india #auction #bollywood": [["Aishwarya Rai", "PERSON"], ["Mumbai", "GPE"]], "NEW: There have been numerous #COVID19 outbreaks on recent cruise ship voyages. @CDCDirector has extended the previous No Sail Order to prevent the spread of COVID-19 among crew onboard. https://t.co/OTWJgCN8wQ https://t.co/sbHX4p907F": [["@CDCDirector", "ORG"], ["No Sail Order", "PRODUCT"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], "@joshtpm We just posted new numbers. Missing the private labs is going to hurt transparency quite severely we think. -@alexismadrigal": [], "Although the number of #COVID19 cases in most states continued to decline over the last 7 days COVID-19 is widespread in many areas especially the South &amp; West. As of Aug. 25 the US reported nearly 1000 deaths a day over the last week. See more data: https://t.co/441ntP6EUZ. https://t.co/HvW3SFqa11": [["the last 7 days", "DATE"], ["COVID-19", "DATE"], ["South", "LOC"], ["West", "LOC"], ["Aug. 25", "DATE"], ["US", "GPE"], ["nearly 1000", "CARDINAL"], ["the last week", "DATE"]], "UPDATE: #Coronavirus Europe (11 countries) ➡️1.88% to 11.43% of population infected with #COVID19 up to 28th March ➡️Interventions have already impacted control of the epidemic ➡️Interventions have saved between 21000 &amp; 120000 lives 🔰Report https://t.co/lcFch0FxCt https://t.co/Int4MCwQjG": [["11", "CARDINAL"], ["28th March", "DATE"], ["between 21000 &amp", "DATE"], ["120000", "CARDINAL"]], "Indian media outlets claimed that a man in Madhya Pradesh's Khargone passed away from COVID-19.": [["Indian", "NORP"], ["Madhya Pradesh's", "GPE"], ["Khargone", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "FAC"]], "#CoronaVirusUpdates: State-wise details of Total Confirmed #COVID19 cases (till 23 September 2020 8 AM) ➡️States with 1-20000 confirmed cases ➡️States with 20001-140000 confirmed cases ➡️States with 140000+ confirmed cases ➡️Total no. of confirmed cases so far https://t.co/0b55TnqVRH": [["State", "ORG"], ["Total Confirmed #COVID19", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["23 September 2020", "DATE"], ["1-20000", "CARDINAL"], ["20001-140000", "CARDINAL"], ["140000", "CARDINAL"]], "RT @CDCDirector: NEW #COVID19 information is available to help you decide whether to go out and what precautions to take if you do includi…": [], "The Tunisian President Qais Said has ordered the dispatch of a medical delegation to Algeria to help it fight Coved-19.": [["Tunisian", "NORP"], ["Qais Said", "PERSON"], ["Algeria", "GPE"], ["Coved-19", "PRODUCT"]], "@BiomedJ @veryvirology Observation: South Africa is hit hard by TB. And banned HCQ. Worst Corona stats in Africa, which otherwise do great; using anti malarial and Ivermectin routinely, another observation. Well, much better than US and U.K. for sure.": [["South Africa", "GPE"], ["HCQ", "ORG"], ["Africa", "LOC"], ["Ivermectin", "PRODUCT"], ["US", "GPE"], ["U.K.", "GPE"]], "UPDATE: #covid19science #COVID19 in Brazil: ➡️Percentage infected population 3.3% in São Paulo to 10.6% in Amazonas ➡️54% drop in reproduction number R following interventions ➡️R above 1 epidemic not yet under control 🔰Report https://t.co/lcFch0FxCt https://t.co/YoyCPfLAAg": [["Brazil", "GPE"], ["São Paulo", "GPE"], ["Amazonas", "GPE"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "New COVID-NET data reported more than 6000 #COVID19 hospitalizations. Of these almost 2000 had race/ethnicity info. When compared to residents in COVID-NET counties Non-Hispanic black people were disproportionately affected by COVID-19 hospitalizations https://t.co/dTvhftTxuV https://t.co/cei7elmBM7": [["more than 6000", "CARDINAL"], ["these almost 2000", "DATE"], ["Non-Hispanic", "NORP"]], "President Donald Trump attending the recital of Quran verses to fight coronavirus.": [["Donald Trump", "PERSON"], ["Quran", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "📢#CoronaVirusUpdates: 📍#COVID19 India Tracker (As on 21 September 2020 08:00 AM) ➡️Confirmed cases: 5487580 ➡️Recovered: 4396399 (80.1%)👍 ➡️Active cases: 1003299 (18.3%) ➡️Deaths: 87882 (1.6%) #IndiaFightsCorona #IndiaWillWin #StaySafe Via @MoHFW_INDIA https://t.co/A1iirHpkQF": [["📍#COVID19 India Tracker", "ORG"], ["21 September 2020", "DATE"], ["5487580", "CARDINAL"], ["1003299", "CARDINAL"], ["87882", "CARDINAL"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona: #COVID19 testing has become more affordable. Our testing strategy was to increase number of tests and to make it available in areas where most required i.e Andaman &amp; Nicobar Islands Lakshadweep North-East at affordable prices: @ProfBhargava DG @ICMRDELHI https://t.co/yJ85fH0Cl1": [["Nicobar Islands", "LOC"], ["Lakshadweep North-East", "LOC"]], "ibuprofen can make coronavirus (COVID-19) worse.": [], "#IndiaFightsCorona India tests more than 9 lakh samples each day two days in a row. Total #COVID19 tests near a new peak of 4 crore. More than 1 crore tested in past 2 weeks. https://t.co/1LMYJ5XVwz https://t.co/uELDnJx4xE": [["#IndiaFightsCorona India", "ORG"], ["each day", "DATE"], ["two days in a row", "DATE"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["More than 1", "CARDINAL"], ["past 2 weeks", "DATE"]], "2nd week of Jan 🇨🇳 had mapped the genome &amp; shared it with WHO &amp; with wider 🌍. We rapidly published a “how to” on building a PCR test for #COVID19 from our partner lab in 🇩🇪. In the 3rd week WHO identified &amp; began contracting for validated production of these tests-@DrTedros": [["2nd week of Jan 🇨🇳", "DATE"], ["the 3rd week", "DATE"], ["WHO", "ORG"]], "Vila Formosa's cemitery in São Paulo Brazil is opening graves to cause panic on population but there are no burials. The graves remain open.": [["Vila Formosa's", "PERSON"], ["São Paulo", "GPE"], ["Brazil", "GPE"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona: Major highlights of this week: More than 5 crore tests conducted so far. More than 33 lakhs patients have been recovered so far. Case fatality rate is continuously declining; currently stands 1.70%: Secretary @MoHFW_INDIA #StaySafe @ICMRDELHI https://t.co/AfoSxfiLKT": [["this week", "DATE"], ["More than 5", "CARDINAL"], ["More than 33", "CARDINAL"]], "#IndiaFightsCorona: Assessment of #COVID Prevention: It has been estimated that the decision of lockdown by slowing down the progress of pandemic in India prevented 14–29 lakh cases and 37–78 thousand deaths. Details : https://t.co/lz6cP3ICfg #StaySafe #IndiaWillWin https://t.co/QXmTDM9Wiq": [["India", "GPE"], ["14", "CARDINAL"], ["29", "CARDINAL"], ["37–78 thousand", "CARDINAL"]], "Some states have mixed antibody test results into what we thought were viral test result statistics. These antibody tests seem to be a relatively small but still significant percentage of the overall tests completed. From what we know most states have not done this.": [], "RT @minhealthnz: No new cases of #COVID19 to report in New Zealand and 550000 registrations of the NZ COVID Tracer app have been recorded.…": [["New Zealand", "GPE"], ["550000", "CARDINAL"], ["NZ COVID Tracer", "PRODUCT"]], "_A vaccine for COVID-19 has been found._": [["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], "Iranians have published a report saying that coronavirus is a biological warfare.": [["Iranians", "NORP"]], "Canada’s top BDSM doctor says wear a mask, leash, tight leather to prevent spread of COVID-19 #cdnpoli #COVID19 https://t.co/1E7yDlIGBD https://t.co/bffEps28Iy": [["Canada", "GPE"]], "My God!\n\nOpen admission of using Covid 19 as bioweapon!! https://t.co/OUtgBwphiL": [["19", "CARDINAL"]], "CDC has given more than $200M to address #COVID19 health disparities among American Indian &amp; Alaska Native people who have suffered a disproportionate burden of illness. Funding will broaden access to COVID-19 resources across tribal communities. https://t.co/MG8e5TWigl https://t.co/KwoPLuxG4g": [["CDC", "ORG"], ["American", "NORP"], ["Indian", "NORP"], ["Alaska Native", "NORP"], ["19", "CARDINAL"]], "Claims made in the viral video Plandemic include: that the virus was \"manipulated\" in a laboratory setting; that hydroxychloroquine is \"effective against these families of viruses\" and that wearing a mask \"activates\" the virus.": [["Plandemic", "PRODUCT"]], "Coronavirus: North Yorkshire goes into 'full emergency mode' due to rise in cases https://t.co/fqEZaxa3P2": [["North Yorkshire", "GPE"]], "Unfortunately while this method makes the numbers closer in *some* cases it doesn't in many others. Here's a bonus chart (not in the whitepaper) that we generated during this analysis. It shows the range of possible specimen values compared to the CDC's reported number. https://t.co/ZzMgdnTLcG": [["CDC", "ORG"]], "Reese Witherspoon’s Julia Roberts’ And Mila Kunis’ Marriages Suffering Under Coronavirus Quarantine? https://t.co/W1VhJ76HBO": [["Reese Witherspoon", "PERSON"], ["Julia Roberts", "PERSON"], ["Mila Kunis", "PERSON"], ["Marriages Suffering Under Coronavirus Quarantine", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "RT @PIB_India: ▪️ India’s total recoveries cross 23 lakh recovery rate stands at 75.27% ▪️ A total of nearly 3.6 crore tests conducted; T…": [["India", "GPE"], ["23", "CARDINAL"], ["nearly 3.6", "CARDINAL"]], "🚓 Criminal inquiry launched into allegations of poor maternity standards at an NHS trust. https://t.co/Y7lYfCEln2": [["NHS", "ORG"]], "Wisconsin Governor Tony Evers’ administration deemed dentists non-essential.": [["Wisconsin", "GPE"], ["Tony Evers", "PERSON"]], "Medical director at PHE Dr Yvonne Doyle says having both #COVID19 and the flu is a \"very risky situation\" as she encourages people who are invited for a flu vaccine to have it. #KayBurley Live updates: https://t.co/I0Ya5YFTvZ https://t.co/Qs5l3S0YFE": [["PHE", "ORG"], ["Yvonne Doyle", "PERSON"]], "Fourteen new cases of #COVID19 have been reported in Nigeria: 13 in Lagos and 1 in Delta State As at 09:30 pm 9th April there are 288 confirmed cases of #COVID19 reported in Nigeria. Fifty-one have been discharged with seven deaths https://t.co/DuP2SGUiTy": [["Fourteen", "CARDINAL"], ["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["13", "CARDINAL"], ["Lagos", "GPE"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Delta State", "GPE"], ["288", "CARDINAL"], ["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["Fifty-one", "CARDINAL"], ["seven", "CARDINAL"]], "AIIMS (Indian medical institute) team has said that Toddy has medicinal properties to cure coronavirus.": [["AIIMS", "ORG"], ["Indian", "NORP"], ["Toddy", "PERSON"]], "Acc to @MoHFW_INDIA as per the current evidence the period of infectivity starts 2 days prior to onset of #COVID19 symptoms &amp; lasts up to 8 days. The extent &amp; role played by asymptomatic #COVID infections in transmission still remain under investigation: https://t.co/HtiPH2KXcO https://t.co/rhyPPzUPsh": [["@MoHFW_INDIA", "ORG"], ["2 days", "DATE"], ["up to 8 days", "DATE"]], "From a progress report on COVID-19 in the journal \"Nature\":\n\"...Researchers used Vero cells — which do not express TMPRSS2 — in an early study that suggested that the drug chloroquine might work as a treatment for COVID-19.\n1/3": [["COVID-19", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Nature", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "We also found that death data made it more difficult to interpret our metric. When there were major changes in Rt it was unclear if this was from changes in cases or deaths. Death data is still important to consider such as in a separate metric which we are working on.": [], "A government minister claims that Papad help produce antibodies to fight COVID-19 infection.": [["Papad", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], ".@WHO reconsiders the airborne nature of #COVID19. https://t.co/RGcG9pddNy": [], "After all the depressing news, came across something so true and motivating. My level of respect for Mr Ratan Tata is inexplicable...": [["Ratan Tata", "PERSON"]], "Texas reported 4k new confirmed cases yesterday with some caveats. Today the state reported 3129 — without the caveats. https://t.co/1pGhGkmILK": [["Texas", "GPE"], ["4k", "CARDINAL"], ["yesterday", "DATE"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["3129", "CARDINAL"]], "A psychiatrist fears that people may be using COVID-sorting similar to serosorting in AIDS as a way to choose a sexual partner. https://t.co/esecZBkz4W": [], "Tuberculosis (TB) has a higher death rate than coronavirus.": [], "The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention applied for an \"illegal\" patent related to the virus that causes SARS.": [["The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention", "ORG"]], "Trump announced that Roche Medical Company will launch the vaccine next Sunday, and millions of doses are ready from it !!!": [["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Roche Medical Company", "ORG"], ["next Sunday", "DATE"], ["millions", "CARDINAL"]], "Acc to @WHO people should NOT wear #facemasks while exercising as sweat can make a #mask wet/damp which may reduce the ability to breathe comfortably. If you are exercising outside kindly maintain a distance of 2m else you may workout at home. #COVID19 #Covid_19 #COVIDー19 https://t.co/IAqtKAyRL7": [], "We’re starting to see evidence that long-term exposure to air pollution—which disproportionately affects communities of color &amp; low-income communities—is linked to COVID-19 death rates. It's past time we treat pollution like the threat to our health it is. https://t.co/3GD15s3xSy": [["19", "CARDINAL"]], "We are pleased to announce the inclusion of the General Sani Abacha State Specialist Hospital Yobe to the NCDC Molecular Laboratory Network. There are currently 62 laboratories with the capacity to test for #COVID19 in the #NCDCLabNetwork #TakeResponsibility https://t.co/DZjuSllsPc": [["the General Sani Abacha State Specialist Hospital Yobe", "ORG"], ["the NCDC Molecular Laboratory Network", "ORG"], ["62", "CARDINAL"]], "A video about the coronavirus circulates in WhatsApp that, when opened, hacks the cell phone \"in 10 seconds\".": [["WhatsApp", "PRODUCT"]], "Nearly 22000 deaths have occurred in long-term facilities in the South—almost 14000 in June July and August. Georgia and Florida have seen their highest death tolls in the past four weeks—over 350 a week in Florida and over 100 a week in Georgia. https://t.co/RC56clVQ1e": [["Nearly 22000", "CARDINAL"], ["South", "LOC"], ["almost 14000", "CARDINAL"], ["June July", "DATE"], ["August", "DATE"], ["Georgia", "GPE"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["the past four weeks", "DATE"], ["350", "CARDINAL"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["over 100", "CARDINAL"], ["Georgia", "GPE"]], "RT @MoHFW_INDIA: #CoronaVirusUpdates #IndiaFightsCorona - Total #COVID19 Recoveries are 677422. - Recovery rate stands at 62.86%. -…": [["677422", "CARDINAL"]], "Every worker on the front lines of the fight against COVID-19 deserves protections and accommodations that keep them and their families safe. I'm glad to see states stepping up to support folks — employers must do the same. https://t.co/QClURuStbV": [["COVID-19", "LAW"]], "In Latest Move to Stop Coronavirus, Trump Urges Fed to Cut Interest Rates His Heavily Indebted Company Pays https://t.co/0wGbfhqtOP": [], "Brazil’s #coronavirus crisis is out of control. https://t.co/01ODoDGGyq https://t.co/O1kzbfpREW": [["Brazil", "GPE"]], "Govt is providing money to bereaved families of COVID-19 victims.": [["19", "CARDINAL"]], "@HSELive You should also high-dose with Vitamin D. Extensive clinical evidence that sufficient Vitamin D reduces severity of Covid-19. Hospital protocol for Covid-19 in France to immediately test for and treat Vit D deficiency. Chronic Vit D deficiency in Ireland – why no public campaign?": [["Covid-19", "ORG"], ["France", "GPE"], ["Ireland", "GPE"]], "NEWS! ‘Loss of taste’ added to COVID-19 symptoms as government recommends self-isolation for anyone who recently enjoyed Mrs Brown’s Boys https://t.co/5ZhFvnHWJb https://t.co/QAjJtAeo7e": [["19", "CARDINAL"], ["Brown", "PERSON"]], "@OdoyleCharlotte @GovLarryHogan @GovRonDeSantis Just noting: @GovRonDeSantis and the Florida health department do actually put out the most complete statistics that we've seen from a state government. -@alexismadrigal": [["GovRonDeSantis", "ORG"], ["Florida", "GPE"]], "#Coronavirus surges in Arizona. https://t.co/zOIdYIEnGK": [["#Coronavirus", "ORG"], ["Arizona", "GPE"]], "Colombia is the country with less cases and deaths for coronavirus per inhabitant in America.": [["Colombia", "GPE"], ["America", "GPE"]], "10 Road Trip Essentials https://t.co/sB9hzYG2MK #coronavirus #travel #vacation #list #tipsadvice #roadtrips": [["10", "CARDINAL"]], "@tangerinelaw @JohnsHopkinsEPI Some of it is time. It takes time for the deaths to come. The other part is that it's spiky: deaths come in much higher numbers when the population is vulnerable and the hospital system gets overwhelmed (Italy) or gets surprised (KirklandWA). -@alexismadrigal": [["Italy", "GPE"]], "Practice social distancing by putting space between yourself and others. Continue to practice healthy habits like washing your hands for at least 20 seconds and staying home if you’re sick to help slow the spread of #COVID19. Learn more: https://t.co/tt49zOn1hf. https://t.co/jiv8rCeZzY": [], "A banner with a swastika, ???Trump??� and ???Pence??� is from a Michigan coronavirus protest.": [["Trump", "PERSON"], ["Pence", "PERSON"], ["Michigan", "GPE"]], "RT @Surgeon_General: Are you concerned about possible #COVID19 symptoms and/or exposure? Consult the @apple screening tool developed w/ @Wh…": [], "Pictures of people stranded on hospital beds claimed to be Italians not coping with the pressures of COVID-19 cases; India should learn from Italy's mistakes and not step out of the house in the 21-day lockdown": [["Italians", "NORP"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["India", "GPE"], ["Italy", "GPE"], ["21-day", "DATE"]], "Some of the worst viral disease outbreaks in recent years – SARS, Ebola and likely #coronavirus – originated in bats, a new study has proposed an answer to why diseases that originate in bats are so deadly. https://t.co/wYZBDVrqsH #coronavirus": [["recent years", "DATE"]], "Coronavirus: John Lewis Partnership axes staff bonus as it slumps to £635m loss https://t.co/kQJOCJTx9T": [["Coronavirus", "ORG"], ["John Lewis Partnership", "ORG"]], "Five new cases of #COVID19 have been reported in Nigeria: 3 in FCT &amp; 2 in Oyo State As at 08:00 pm 27th March there are 70 cases of confirmed #COVID19 reported Nigeria. 3 have been discharged with 1 death. https://t.co/ptbxknBV7b": [["Five", "CARDINAL"], ["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["FCT &amp", "ORG"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Oyo", "GPE"], ["27th March", "DATE"], ["70", "CARDINAL"], ["Nigeria", "GPE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "Covid-19 totally confused about what it’s allowed to do where https://t.co/hKCZmLsibB": [["Covid-19", "PERSON"]], "Coronavirus: 'COVID-19 only takes white people': Researchers battle disease myths in South Africa https://t.co/h16rbDeJaT": [["COVID-19", "ORG"], ["South Africa", "GPE"]], "For data observers one key takeaway is that the lag in reporting deaths may vary widely between states that use the different methods.": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "It's not entirely clear how the record numbers of new cases will translate into deaths from COVID-19. Here's why it's complicated: https://t.co/ZXFERIyS6I https://t.co/BgyADNSieh": [], "Image of COVID-19 infected Indonesian doctor Hadio Ali watching his daughters from a distance as he bids them final goodbye; the image is said to be posted by his wife.": [["Indonesian", "NORP"], ["Hadio Ali", "PERSON"]], "13464 cases of #COVID19Nigeria Discharged: 4206 Deaths: 365 A breakdown of cases by state can be found via https://t.co/A0NkMvZqE5 #TakeResponsibility https://t.co/toGrZ6v2AD": [["4206", "CARDINAL"], ["365", "CARDINAL"]], "“This is about giving the hospitals that capacity they need to get people through the doors.” Health minister Edward Argar explains the additional £150 million funding to expand and upgrade hospital A&amp;Es in England. #KayBurley: https://t.co/apswxjCfGw https://t.co/xnHsJRblFF": [["Edward Argar", "PERSON"], ["England", "GPE"]], "Schedules for the sale of milk newspapers grocery and medical stores have been issued by the Mumbai Police commissioner.": [["Mumbai Police", "ORG"]], "490 new cases of #COVID19Nigeria; Lagos-142 FCT-60 Bayelsa-54 Rivers-39 Delta-37 Oyo-30 Kaduna-26 Imo-23 Enugu-19 Kwara-17 Gombe-11 Ondo-10 Bauchi-8 Ogun-7 Borno-6 Benue-1 17148 confirmed 5623 discharged 455 deaths https://t.co/wou7Q1PfIo": [["490", "CARDINAL"], ["5623", "CARDINAL"], ["455", "CARDINAL"]], "Researchers warned of a ticking coronavirus time bomb in 2007. 💣 https://t.co/8V4flWNSKr via @undark": [["2007", "DATE"]], "U.S. pediatric COVID-19 cases have jumped 90% in 4 weeks. https://t.co/nSdAf6C3Me": [["U.S.", "GPE"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["4 weeks", "DATE"]], "The recent spike in new #COVID19 cases in India can be attributed to aggressive testing &amp; tracing mechanism employed by GoI. This spike in cases is not worrisome as long as the diagnosis is done in time &amp; the #MortalityRate remains low with high #RecoveryRate. (1/2) https://t.co/Ug4akjc15A": [["India", "GPE"], ["GoI", "ORG"]], "The variation between states/territories is also fascinating. DC told the Washington Post it doesn't report probables because it doesn't have any. Delaware meanwhile with a comparable total case count reports nearly 1000 probable cases.": [["DC", "ORG"], ["the Washington Post", "ORG"], ["Delaware", "GPE"], ["nearly 1000", "CARDINAL"]], "Goodnight this is where the US stands now :: 🏠✔️Stay At Home: 37 States ....🚶‍♀️Social Distancing: 11 States 👀 Limited Intervention: 1 State": [["US", "GPE"], ["37", "CARDINAL"], ["11", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "Mixing aspirin paracetamol honey and lemon cures COVID-19.": [], "Six coronavirus cases confirmed in Wichita Kansas.": [["Six", "CARDINAL"], ["Wichita", "GPE"], ["Kansas", "GPE"]], "RT @DDIndialive: #COVID19 Testing Status: ICMR (@ICMRDELHI) tests a total of 144910 samples from 130792 individuals as on 9th April 202…": [["144910", "CARDINAL"], ["130792", "CARDINAL"], ["9th April 202", "DATE"]], "The Chairman of the Republican Party of Texas said the recovery rate for COVID-19 is 99.9% in Texas. That’s False. @PolitiFactTexas https://t.co/GmUXoVT2Dh https://t.co/ltIHWPchJM": [["the Republican Party of Texas", "ORG"], ["Texas", "GPE"]], "Dr. Dana Meaney-Delman was a part of the emergency responses to Zika and the Ebola outbreak. Read her experience as she helped take on #COVID19: https://t.co/3v15grreJZ. https://t.co/pbKnNMF6HR": [["Dana Meaney-Delman", "PERSON"], ["Zika", "GPE"]], "RT @drharshvardhan: India sees an unprecedented surge in Recoveries ! 👉Nearly 75000 recoveries in last 24 hours 👉Total number of Recover…": [["India", "GPE"], ["Nearly 75000", "CARDINAL"]], "COVID-19 Update ​ ​ We have 5 new cases of COVID-19 in the community. 4 are Auckland-based and 1 is connected to the 2 Tokoroa cases and is currently in Waikato Hospital. ​ ​ This brings our total number of active cases to 101.": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Auckland", "GPE"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Tokoroa", "GPE"], ["Waikato Hospital", "GPE"], ["101", "CARDINAL"]], "417 new cases of #COVID19Nigeria; Lagos-207 Kaduna-44 Ondo-38 Abia-28 Anambra-21 Plateau-20 Bauchi-13 Oyo-9 Ebonyi-9 Delta-7 Edo-7 Enugu-6 Niger-3 Gombe-2 Ogun-1 FCT-1 Kano-1 49485 confirmed 36834 discharged 977 deaths https://t.co/nNc9UYKU34": [["417", "CARDINAL"], ["36834", "CARDINAL"], ["977", "CARDINAL"]], "In the latest updates from today #NewYork is now 🟢 green on our threat scale ➡️ on track to contain COVID. This change is due to the number of #contacttracers they've recently hired and is a big testament to the state has done to control COVID. https://t.co/wcSmatoG5C": [["today", "DATE"], ["#NewYork", "ORG"]], "COVID-19 will result in tens of thousands of excess cancer deaths according to a new NCI model. https://t.co/rIxuqqG0rw #EHA2020 https://t.co/7Q9WeuPTqc": [["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"], ["tens of thousands", "CARDINAL"], ["NCI", "ORG"]], "For a breakdown of cases by states in real time please see https://t.co/zQrpNeOfet Currently; Lagos- 24 FCT- 6 Ogun- 2 Ekiti- 1 Oyo- 1 Edo- 1 Total: 35 confirmed cases #COVID19Nigeria": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["35", "CARDINAL"]], "The departament of Guaviare in Colombia has 10 cases of coronavirus.": [["Guaviare", "GPE"], ["Colombia", "GPE"], ["10", "CARDINAL"]], "We’re still learning about how #COVID19 affects animals but it appears that people can spread the virus to animals in some situations. Until we know more limit contact with pets if you are sick or feeling sick. For more info see: https://t.co/H8NS2GTd4x. https://t.co/uGEbo1su2O": [], "The governor of Sao Paulo contracted COVID-19 after being vaccinated with the Sinovac Biotech vaccine.": [["Sao Paulo", "GPE"], ["COVID-19", "PRODUCT"]], "Iranian Islamic medicine 'specialist' claims camel urine cures coronavirus infections iran\". Arab News": [["Iranian", "NORP"], ["Islamic", "NORP"], ["Arab News", "ORG"]], "The WHO confirmed asymptomatic persons can't transmit the coronavirus and are not infectious": [["WHO", "ORG"]], "#IndiaFightsCoro